ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo ooooo o
There's a door that only opens from inside
We bring our doubts and we set them aside
Eyes on the candle, mind on the vow
Say it's off to say it now
A circle of echoes, a glittering rule
Everybody's holding, nobody's fool
We trade our questions for something to hold
Warm little eyes and a palm of gold
If you feel the pull, don't fight the tide
Let it take you, let it decide your-
devotion is a kind of art so we cut our pieces of the heart smile for the
mirror smile come in and in the air like a promised land we wear the silence
like velvet tray we stitch it tight through the things I'm saying
some of the stumbles we call it fate we call the hunger a sacred gate if you feel the
boot on count the cars you can't be found if you won't be lost your old voice
fades in the baseline boom your new voice blooms in a crowded
Love knows keepin' me warm
yesterday. Good ones. I have some good horoscopes today. I'm going to wait for
people to get in here and stuff, but I made some good songs.
Born naked to the sky
Every secret on your skin
Every watch you're asking for
But the truth is your armor
And the shadows can't compete
You were forced to walk in daylight
Where the fragile fear to speak
They tried to bury a thunder
Again, the cowards feel their shame You are the storm
The crack in the sleep in mind
You shake the dreamers from illusions
They were terrified to find
Trolls howl at your reflection
For you mirror what they hide
You are the truth they long avoided
The judge they can't divide
But the wound
Justice in your spine
Your power is the punchline
Your laughter is divine
They judge you by the ancient laws that own
horoscopes written for every sign and then I have my labyrinth cards. I'll do
free three-card readings for anybody in the chat. If you'd like more, simply look
at the bottom of the screen, you can get a more detailed reading. Okay, but I'll
start with the horoscopes. All people get in here. We're starting with cap
Because we're in Capricorn right now. We're in the sign of Capricorn. This is my sign.
My birthday is in a week. Seven days. I think no, I can get eight days.
Let's come in quick. So for Capricorn, which is my sign.
Aw. Yeah, so Capricorn. I have a prophecy for Capricorn this new year.
Capricorns, you will accidentally become the responsible one in the group chat. You didn't
For Capricorn, your 2026 theme will be strategic dominance.
I have an omen for you.
A checklist will actually get finished.
So do this.
Say no once per day, like it's a sacred rite.
Now your online prophecy is going to be,
you become unstoppable the moment
you stop negotiating with your own goals.
So this year, Capricorn, your patience turns into leverage.
You'll feel an internal pressure to lock in, and it won't be subtle, your tolerance for
nonsense drops, your standards rise, and suddenly the world starts meeting you where you've
been standing the whole time.
Money and momentum improve when you stop doing unpaid emotional labor, and start treating
your time like an asset.
Your best wins come from being from boring consistency.
Fewer promises, more receipts, people may call you intense, good, that's just them noticing
you're done playing small.
We are now at Aquarius, I'm going to clip that by the way, Aquarius, a weird idea you've
joked about becomes your best plan.
Your 2026 theme will be chaotic innovation.
Your lucky omen this next year will be a stranger says exactly what you needed to hear.
So do this, build the thing before you explain it.
Your one line prophecy this year is your weird idea is the roadmap.
Aquarius, your future shows up dressed like a random obsession. Follow it. This year rewards experimentation, not perfection.
So your job is to prototype your life. Test new formats, new people, new routines, new tech, new aesthetics. The moment you try to make it
make sense to everyone, it loses power.
So keep some plans private until they're strong.
Social circles shift, allow grow a few rooms and discover new ones that actually speak your language. Your freedom expands the second you stop asking permission.
And hope you enjoy that Aquarius now for Pisces
Pisces the prophecy for this 2026 for you is your intuition will be right and you will still doubt it for comedic effect
Your theme for next year will be soft power
Lucky omen a dream that you won't that won't you forget do this create a boundary that feels like a love spell
Your one line prophecy on Pisces is your sensitivity is a superpower when you guard it
So Pisces you're entering a year where your emotional radar becomes a profit center
If you stop letting it drain you your gift is knowing what's real, but your lesson is not rescuing what's broke
expect creative surges, sharper instincts, and a stronger know that doesn't require guilt.
Relationships improve when you choose clarity over fantasy.
If someone confuses you on purpose, that's your answer.
Your best move is simple. Protect your sleep, protect your energy, protect what your art.
Everything else aligns behind that, okay?
That's for Pisces now. We have our Aries or babies of the zodiac our Rams, okay?
So Aries your prophecy is you'll start something small and accidentally launch a movement
Your theme for 2026 will be momentum. Okay, do this
Choose one target stop shadow boxing everything your lucky omen will be a compliment from someone intimidating
A prophecy in one line for you is pick a lane, become a legend in it, and for Aries.
This year is about a decisive action, not adrenaline.
You'll be tempted to start 10 things at once, but your real power comes from committing
to one mission long enough to see results.
Watch for ego traps, arguing, proving, clapping back, that's still your focus.
The quiet flex is building what others perform.
Career or creative output levels, when you treat discipline like your new love language.
they will go up. The more you aim the luck you get, you're not here to be busy, you're
here to win. That's for Aries.
Tourists' Prophecy for Tourists, 2026,
you'll upgrade your comfort and call it self-care.
That'll be correct.
Your theme next year will be Luxury with Purpose.
Your lucky omen will be finding money in a pocket
like the universe tips you.
So do this, invest in quality, people, tools and habits.
Your Prophecy this year, slow is fine, stagnant is not.
So for 2026, tourists, your year,
is a steady climb, but only if you stop confusing familiar with safe, you'll feel pulled toward
better standards, better environment, better health, better relationships, better tools.
And that's not vanity, that's alignment. Financial growth improves when you simplify.
Fewer subscriptions, fewer draining obligations, maybe fewer people. You're building a life you
actually want to live in, not just survive it. If you feel stubborn this year, aim it at your goals,
Prophecy for Gemini is you'll talk your way into an opportunity and then panic because it works.
Your 2026 theme will be major career networking.
Lucky Omen, a perfectly timed meme, is in your future, right?
So do this, write it down, your brain is not a filing cabinet.
Your prophecy, Gemini, is your mouth opens doors, your follow-through keeps them open.
So your horoscope for this year is your, this year upgrades your voice, your writing, speaking, pitching, storytelling, content, all of it.
You can't keep improvising your way through everything. You need systems that capture your
lightning. Expect new connections, collaborations, and sudden limitations. But the best ones come
when you show up prepared, not just charming. Don't over-explain your plans to skeptical people.
Build quietly and reveal loudly. If you commit to one consistent platform or routine,
you'll be scary successful. Your magic is momentum plus documentation.
We have cancers in the room.
Cancers are crabs.
Your prophecy this year is you'll stop protecting people
from consequences, the earth will keep spinning.
Your 2026 theme, cancers is emotional leadership.
Your lucky omen is someone finally says, I get it.
Do this, let your care have conditions.
It's not cruel, it's clean.
Your one line prophecy is care, but don't carry.
and your horoscope this year for next year.
The next year teaches you the difference
between love and leakage.
You're still you, warm, loyal, protective,
but you're done being the unpaid therapist
for people who refuse to grow.
Home, family, and inner peace become priorities.
And you only make changes that look selfish
to anyone benefiting from your overgiving.
Good.
Your intuition is sharp, trust the feeling
that tells you when something is off,
even when it's subtle.
You'll thrive and create structure around your emotions,
routines, boundaries, and safe circle.
Protecting your heart is how you expand it.
That was for our cancers.
Leo, your prophecy for next year
is you'll be admired by being brave.
While you're privately terrified, iconic.
Yeah, your 2026 theme is spotlight alchemy.
Lucky omen, a photo where you look powerful for no reason.
Do this. Accept praise without deflecting it, like a dodgeball.
Your one-line prophecy is your confidence is contagious. Vaccinate your doubt.
Okay, paragraph for you.
You glow or glow up this year is less look at me and more watch what I build you'll be toward a poll toward bigger visibility creative work leadership performing branding and the universe is basically yelling stop hiding the only danger is seeking
validation from people who can't afford your dreams choose audiences that celebrate you without trying to shrink you.
Love and friendship improve when you stop performing strength and start practicing honesty.
Your new flex's consistency show up, ship the work, repeat.
You're not chasing attention, you're creating impact.
And clip that one.
Virgos.
Proposy for Virgos.
You'll optimize one thing and accidentally fix your whole life.
Your 2026 theme is elegant systems.
Your lucky omen will be a perfectly labeled folder.
So do this.
and your online prophecy is systems beat mood.
So for Virgos in this next year,
this next year will be a masterclass
in small improvements that compound into new reality.
Your mind is sharp,
but your growth comes from reducing friction,
better habits, cleaner schedule, cleaner commitments,
fewer energy leaks,
health and wellness respond fast when you're trying to stop.
I'm trying to solve everything and simply doing the basics consistently. You'll also get pickier about who gets access to you
That's a win not a flaw when you focus on completion over critique
You'll work becomes unstoppable like good enough be a rocket fuel
And that was for Virgos Libras
Prophecy for Libras, you'll choose yourself and call it balance.
It's also correct.
Your 2026 theme will be standard, so your lucky omen is a sudden wave of clarity mid-conversation.
So do this, make decisions faster.
Your peace is worth the speed.
A prophecy for you is peace is the prize, not the compromise.
Paragraph for you. This year is about clearer choices and fewer mixed signals, especially from yourself.
You'll be confronted with situations where you can either keep things nice or make them real. Choose real.
Relationships improve when you stop negotiating your boundaries like they're optional.
Career and money grow when you stop waiting for the perfect moment and start moving with confidence.
You'll also refine your aesthetic and environment. Beauty becomes medicine this year. The more you honor your own standards, the more
the right people will rise to meet you okay we got scorpios in the house
Scorpio a prophecy for you is your silence will scare the right people
your honesty will attract the right ones um your 2020 and 2016 will be magnetism
Lucky Omen for Scorpio the secret revealed the exact right time. Don't or do do this
Don't chase closure choose power one-mind prophecy. Don't explain yourself to people committed to misunderstanding you
Scorpio this year turns your intensity into clarity. You'll see through people faster
Cut through nonsense quicker stop offering access to anyone who frees
Trust like a game big transformation energy career privates relationship truth deep personal upgrades your
Power move is restraint, knowing when to speak, to move, to let people reveal themselves without
interruption. Money improves when you stop underpricing your insight and start treating
your expertise like a premium offering. You're not becoming colder, you're becoming precise.
And finally, we have Sagittarius, a prophecy for Sagittarius. You'll book a trip,
your 2020-60 will be expansion.
Your lucky omen will be a random, in quotes, invitation.
So do this, say yes, the next chapter starts
when you move.
And Sagittarius, in 2026, the year will want you out of the box, physically, mentally, creatively.
You'll feel restless, and that's not a problem. It's a compass.
Learning, traveling, reaching, content, and a big vision, planning, are favored.
But you'll need to avoid burning yourself out, chasing every shiny thing.
Choose adventures that build your future, not just your memories.
New friendships and opportunities will arrive when you say yes to rooms that intimidate you a little.
Your luck is real, but it's activated by action.
Move first, clarity follows.
And those are your horoscopes.
Hey Alex, what's up?
Hold on.
Tripp and sip, can you come up and give me a terror rating?
Tripp and sip, I don't know about that.
Don't know about that trip and sip and you're like making your same weird things. I don't know I'm talking about you can come up and talk if you want
There's the link
Hey Alex. Hey vampire or
Bad bad just scope. Why is you so gay? I don't know. I was born that way
Is my kitty cat why the nor he cut the person called me gay in the chat
The nor is like I'm his wife leave me alone leave my husband alone. Okay. She's alright. Okay. We have a trippin sip
Hello
Hi, how are you?
I'm alright. How about you?
I'm just peachy today. Okay, so you said you want to give me a reading or just like me to give you
Yeah, I mean, you know, I've seen you give readings a few times and
I thought maybe I'd get into it, you know a little bit. I've been doing a little research and I got some cards
Are you joking or is this being serious? No, I'm serious. Okay. What kind of cards do you have?
What are your, what's your deck? Just I got a card, whatever was on Amazon, the first thing I looked up for tarot cards
Be a writer. Okay. Well, I'm interested, but it's not like you take it seriously or you make it a complete joke
One or the other don't like pretend it's serious and then make it a joke, right? I mean
Don't I don't play it with you know things like this, you know tarot cards are really serious
Is it the new Pokemon to play with the dark arts? Is it the new Pokemon deck?
All right, so are you ready you want your first card? I'm ready trip. Go ahead. All right, so
Hold on me get it out here
So your first card is
Looks like the litter box
Okay, what this card means is that you have first you are
off the show. That's what that card means. Okay. Anywhere. Well, I'm glad he didn't get through
it. Yeah. Well, yeah. Bye. And you can like take me off your room. I don't even care.
I mean, just like, why do you have to be a dick? I said, make it an absolute joke or
serious. No, you had to pretend like it was serious and then say the litter box. No.
Hey Alex, come on, come on, Alex. I might miss you. Where have you been?
It's been terrible, Alex. I won't almost quit YouTube. I'm like, I'm
Just struggling. Thank you, Alex. Where's Rudy? Rudy's right here.
Why are you Rudy? Rudy's around somewhere. I just pulled a thorn out of Trix's face, too. Oh my god. It was terrible.
Look it, I'll show you what it was.
He had a cactus or something in his face. Just pulled it out. Ouch.
know okay well the litter box I don't know let's predict the next one so it was
gonna be the next card let me see you're gonna say something about you know
the neutering or something like that okay hey what's up hi Alex
Hey, Ronis my man Ronis. How are you? I'm good, bro
Good to see you. It's been a while. Have you met? How's your Christmas? I haven't seen you since you I'm good. Thank you
My Christmas is good. Thank you so much for asking. I was yours. I you were sick during your Christmas
I was sick. I did
Get a couple gifts from my chat and then it's like, you know, but I missed. Yeah, I miss I know a couple people
They got sick on Christmas something's going around for people. I know got some stomach bug them and throwing up for like two days
I'm a
You know and my birthday is this in on the 7th. So my birthday is coming right up. So it's gonna be better like maybe this year
I'll do my
I went to this place last year this restaurant. It was a nice restaurant. And my mom was like, well, did you bring your ID?
She's like, if you show your ID on your birthday
Everyone whose birthday you got free something right a free treat and they say he's taking lobster
Lobster with a focus page
Yeah, the lobster
Yeah, good good man. Good to see you bro. This is you. I missed you and uh, missed you too. Good happy new year
Ah, look the Rudy. I found Alex. I found my uh, these cards
Your world cards?
Labyrinth. Oh hit me. Hit me baby. I'm not reading these. Okay, I'll get you get a three card reading
I'm gonna give anybody who wants a three card reading for free. Okay, so here we go
They're really cool cards. Actually, they're based on the original like drawings of of Labyrinth
I just didn't just shuffle them a little bit better because they are wait Labyrinth the movie. Yeah. Oh, that's my favorite movie
Yeah, you see David Bowie right here. That's crazy, bro
I just watched that last summer on like
They have a you know when you go in the car
The driving you have that shit here and they play Labyrinth. Oh the driving
Yeah, they do at Corona Park and it's free
That sounds cool. Do they have like awesome? They play all the old school movies. You just go in your car
I think you'd pay for parking like five seven bucks and you just drive into this grass and you watch a free movie in your car
Bro, and it's awesome. That's really cool
Was like um, they did like uh when I was like probably in high school 14 or something like that
I got invited to like a rocky or picture show
Movie like and then you go to like as old it was in Santa Monica or something you go
And it's like there's people on stage like re-enacting the movie while the movie's playing. Oh, yeah, that's cool
I I seen that once in a movie like people on the beach watching people on the stage like
That's crazy
Okay, so little rocker picture show. I never seen that movie or whatever it is
They really get me and it's like the first time you'll watch you like what the hell does that mean like, oh
Can you explain it to me real quick?
This couple I think Janet and Brad or something and it's like Susan Sarandon plays the Janet
I've heard who Brad is they go to this that their car breaks down and like the scary like kind of
Four is and they drop they break down right in front of this big mansion
It's a movie. It's a movie. Yeah, it's a movie.
That's first Tim Curry, too, who plays like the it clown.
That's the guy from Clue, right? That's the butler from Clue. Yeah.
He plays like Dr. Frankfurt or who's like this.
He's created like this kind of like sex slave kind of like hot.
Blonde guy or whatever and then the whole like then he has his servants and there's like you know
Like there's a really scary like kind of I haven't seen it in years. So I don't know these sounds good, bro
It's really good you should you should watch it and it's really good
I should and like music is like we really can give me like the first time I hear they watch it
I'm like, huh, but then it's like then you recognize music and then it's like you like it
water signs are unlovable Hector says, I don't agree with that Hector, right, the water
will take hold exactly the little rocker picture show horror picture show
and
you've got a new friend, Gootham.
Yeah, Gootham is a great friend.
He's from India, South India.
I've only met him before, but yeah, he's from South India.
He's been here almost every night.
I met him on Instagram.
Yeah, he's really cool.
He's from South India, and it's great having
a Hindu friend here.
I'm going to still get a little hit on my,
I can't get my lighter, so I'll screw you right now.
Go with them hit the link with them come up. Say hello
Let's get some readings from the Ronys
Hello, mr. Alex. Hello, mr. Gootham
Welcome
Psychies a really good guy man
And I know him for a while
thank you
You see I got this up. I got this from Minnie Manson sent me a Christmas card. This was like my one of my favorite way
Yeah, so I got this
That's cool because I thought he hated you, right?
This the last time yeah, he was on the show once but then he does like we have talked on his show
He wants to come back to my show, but there's like there's his he signed that it's just like he
Oh, you got a free little package the fridge magnets the stickers the whole shit
The stickers
Look at many
Viva Las Vegas
And signed
Signed, yep, everything's signed
Oh, yeah, this one
This is sticker
Nice, 666
I remember that, he was showing that off
Look green in that
Oh, awesome
Look green screen and then this black one
but that's your new laptop like on the back of it, you know, you know people put like stickers all over the laptops
Yeah, and there's this one too. There's one little star sticker. Nice
There we go and thank you mini Manson for sending me a Christmas card that was like the only Christmas card I got
So what is that a sticker the store sticker? Yeah, that's hilarious. That's the best the star one
I'll get your reading for you Alex. So Alex, let's thank you. Alex between
Okay, let's pop now, okay
Okay, okay
Okay, so this this deck is a little bit different so you got it looks like this this is like a four it looks like a four of cups
Okay
That's like I almost like think of a double date kind of when I think about that. It's like it's like coming together with
For long so what is it? So this is the but it might be those cornucopia is coming together
Okay, so it's okay. Well, it looks like yeah
It looks like a bunch of like different little cornucopia
But they call this is actually called the suit of junk and so it says the four of junk
Advises you to set yourself up for lasting material success by by
building solid foundations and conserving your resources.
Being smart about your finances and investments
will now go on to create long-term stability, okay?
So I think like any kind of financial decisions
you're making right now can actually be good
for your future and stuff like that.
So like I've considered those investments
and things like that and those savings accounts
and anything like that,
because that will kind of set you up
for your long-term and saying, okay?
Then we have ooh, we have the Hierophant. Oh, you have the hoggle. There's hoggle as a Hierophant
Okay, and this is almost like, you know, I always think of the Pope or like, you know
The Catholic Church when I think think of the Hierophant is like this like, you know, it's like kind of like
Intermediary to God, but I'll tell you from this particular book
For Decc it says, the Hierophant values order and tradition and he takes his role in society
just as seriously as Hoggle takes his job in the labyrinth.
So while there's certainly a time and place for rebellion and non-conformity, the Hierophant
warns that current circumstances call for you to fall in line.
respect tradition, listen to the authority figures in your life, whether this refers to managers, mentors, or the Goblin King,
doing as you're told will help you avoid a dreaded trip to the bog of eternal stench, okay?
Like that, you know, remember that bog of eternal stench, you step in it and it's on you forever?
Terrible. Okay, and then finally for Alex and Queen
What do we got? Oh
Okay, we have a tower card for you
There's gonna be a big shake-up something something really big this year
But and it might be in something of something to do with your tradition or religion. Hey, we've got them here to say hi to you too
There's got them
and I'll tell you what the tower in this
Tower says in here
I think you can hear me with my religion or my a Gotham
Yeah, but it's like but it's what says a tower represents and expected sometimes catastrophic change such as
Experiences with Tobias whisked away by goblins to Jared's castle though the words catastrophe and destruction often conjure fear
The tower's message isn't negative
Destruction can be necessary to clear space. Exactly. You need destruction to restart bro like 9-11, right?
Destruction is just an opportunity for rebirth. That's how I take this job
Hours in that car there's hours in that card in the moon
The adventure venture Sarah encounters while making her way through the labyrinth to rescue him leads her to growth
Trust that this period of chaos
was ultimately bring about greater clarity and insight.
So there you go, Alex.
I hope that.
Thank you so much, brother.
That was awesome.
Yeah.
So I mean, Gotham, look, he has a shirt.
I love it.
Gutham.
Is it Gutham or Gotham?
Gotham.
Nice to meet you, bro.
I don't like to meet you.
You're the best.
He's very good looking.
I would have to Gotham.
W, W.
What the fuck is he saying?
I've been watching my new videos. I don't know if you've seen some of my new videos, but yeah
I'm like actually like do some animation in them and
Putting like the themes in together making them like a lot better and so I'm really I'm gonna pay you for that detailed reading
Psych but I was gonna super try you but that makes no sense because you'll get it in fucking a month
So when we I get dropped here, I'll send you I'll sell you
cards then I'll give you like a few more cards so here. No you don't have to let's say you had a goth cool you know Gotham. Yeah, I can say I had a Gotham. Well give Gotham a card. Yeah, you really would like a card or a Gotham?
It's Gotham, a tarot reader as well Gotham. What do you, what's his deal? What do you, what's your deal Gotham? I can play, I can play or what is it? Do you hear me? Oh yeah. How it works, how it works I can play. Hello. Hi. Hey.
Tripp this is trippin sip actually trippin sip. He does he does the the rumble the rumble my man trippin sip
There's so many trips. There's a trip cake a trip and sip
Are you brothers are you related what's going on here with the trips?
They just clip people's panels and like make fun of or like try to make it their own panel of other people's bullshit
That's the funniest thing to me
I like how he's making shows because being able to lead their lives and you know people to lead their lives
Yeah, but bro, you've got to be such a loser to do that because you can't make your own content
So your whole life is
Clipping other people's content and trying to make your own panel
That's how I see it. How big of a loser do you have to be?
To make a channel of all the people's clip their channel like shut up
Clips it's the whole stream. I have a program that just
So why you watch psyches panel and then clip it and make it
What's the point of that archive it because everybody deletes their shit and if people miss stuff they want to watch it
Well, no that I like no no now that I like now. He's my boy
You know I'm saying no, no, I need him on my team. So you archive everything. Yeah, I love that
Yeah, because a lot she gets a race dropped home bomb my man got it in the archives
We can't you dick you're in the kitchen
Good
the
Yeah
To go to war for anybody
It's an analogy an analogy
That everyone in the army doesn't know each other right but then they have to and they become brothers like it's so cool
You know, oh, and I really do believe in the brotherhood of humanity like and I guess recognize the other human beings as
part of us
Yeah
This guy is the hot India guy has he ever been on the panel before is he is he coming for calling in from India?
looking dude
Microsoft tech support. He looks good in green. The green is working for him the green shirt
Oh and trackable is here to put us to bed hit the late date. I feel like he's called me before
Oh, yeah, hello, sir, I have your shim yard customer service
Damn
Getting racist up here. I love in the in the customer service. They're very nice people like I've hardly ever had a no
They're not most of them are scammers. They're scam old ladies
This guy is but
Cool peeps, but there's no way channels Kate is popping on the panel. She's lying
the
And anybody who I feel anyone does I know like you're kind of joking trip and chips
But if you if you want a reading I got a three-card reading for you or Gotham or anybody in the chat, too
Like I'm just in the mood. So I'm gonna be doing more folk more focus on my terror readings
Like my cats are all fed. They're all clean happy today and
So you don't have to worry about that.
Trip wasn't talking shit about Javy's Cowboys.
I know, and I do want to say like someone would think,
oh, did Javy's Cowboys, was he,
she giving Christine information about, like, about someone?
Well, I wasn't really talking any about that.
I was more so talking about when she had her accident.
And I guess she, Christine said that she had told,
Jamie had told her that she needed
a facial reconstruction surgery or something.
No, it wasn't that bad.
I don't think it was that bad.
That's what Christine told us at Jamie Toler.
No, that's a lie.
Because we were impacted with Jamie the whole time.
Listen.
And she was like, we're coming to the hospital.
She told a few people in a voice call,
like a week after or so after her accident
and said that she said she never needed.
Facial reconstruction surgery didn't I was just trying to get to the bottom of who was possibly making up or misremembering
Remembering that's one of the best lines. I've heard in my life
Misremembering wow
That's a good one, bro. That's what everyone does up here. They misremember shit
My boy trip just hit it
Christine said that she could be she could have
Because of the trauma from the injury she she could have a member said something she didn't mean
Telling Christine I was in Christine's discord
There's only, I just remember seeing Bronzeberg there.
That's like, there's a hardly anything.
Well, that's, that's what I've seen.
The two people that people were saying was Jamie's Cowboys and Bronzeberg.
But honestly, I don't really know.
I don't have any, any, any, any intuition or anything like I could say on it.
So.
Okay, well, yeah, I was just clearing up like I do think it's Bronzeberg telling Christine about everything because it turns out
I text message Peter one time be as Peter sent
My message is to Bronzeberg like oh, here's some trackable and auto
Hi guys
What a sight for sunrise you're on trackable seriously man my man
to all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Is that actually an auto person or is that that Paul guy pretending to be?
There he is. There he is. Let me see.
No, auto is the best.
He has a little bald head.
Yeah, you saw his little head peek out. Look at him.
Look at that little head peeking out.
No, don't let me, don't let me crash the stream, bro.
Just don't want to crash out, bro.
Floaty diamonds waiting for you, baby.
Are you wearing a shirt? Are you have lotion out today?
I don't know.
I just continue with the party, I just continue with the party everybody, I just continue, continue, continue.
Okay, here, I'm gonna fix it, I'm gonna fix it.
Hey, Holmes, how you doing?
There he is, Otto!
Okay, well, he's a beat-a-synth, well, you know.
Pick me up some Taco Bell, Holmes.
I'm not a beat-a-synth.
Yo quiero Taco Bell. Yeah, he's actually Canadian. So he's I mean according to same and be that was was apparently cooking me when I was on panel
It was like a conversation about the whole thing with Kate and Christine and be the
first up with Kate and I was
Basically just saying like yeah, I don't agree with doxing or anything like that
But you know if if you want like like with beta she wants to press like harassment charges for real
She can't be she can't be you know
Saying shit about Kate and you know egging her on basically by you know calling her names and stuff like that because
It's just gonna be an endless back and forth like I feel like you really don't want that shit to happen to you
Then you should just
I try to ignore them as much as you can.
That's how I say it.
Any side, like what Kate does is right or anything,
but I'm just saying, like.
Yeah, it's been a back and forth and it's like, it's not just like, you know, one person doing it and then the other person is just like, I mean, totally silent and something. It's like, it's a back and forth and it's a terrible things about Kate and, you know, I know Kate said some bad things.
at least a better understanding of each other.
I like it a lot.
Oh yeah, and I mean, a lot of them,
like why I was bringing it up is I think we,
you know, me, Bita, and Christine, you know,
we had a good conversation about it
and it wasn't anything like,
where we're like yelling at each other
or like, you know, we hate each other over it.
It's just fucking, you know, panel talk.
Yeah, this is like, you know, really it's like, you know,
there's like,
I mean, things can get serious online, but it's like, you know, at the end of the day,
it's supposed to be more fun than serious.
This is, like, how I relaxed and whined, and...
It's not supposed to be a new source of stress
Bro, it's what we come home after work to unwind and people are going crazy and making like stress and threats like what the fuck
Yeah
Especially in this community, we should be at least have each other's backs because there's so many outside the community
That will come in an attack. They don't have to explain they take everything to heart man every little word. Oh my god
We all can be sensitive to things like that, and especially because we like don't control the narrative and stuff and other people are trying to maybe control it on us, but we can always have our own show and like put on our own, our own beliefs and our own side of the story too.
And so, I mean, I'll just have to rest with that, but it's like, you know, at least I can have the freedom to say what I want to say to and, you know,
I think it's all good. It's all good. So how's everyone doing like it's nice having everyone here
I take a couple days off you um, I think you have to I haven't
Haven't seen you do anything to her. I heard you talk about her
So whoever quick boy less is knows knows our history
Unfinished garage garage boys slow down on the bruski's
Swinboy less is that les
It's somebody from tbp or like that knows us
and, you know, on for this garage, yes, show that on for the ceiling, fuck you, twig boy, I've been going at this pick for four years over that shit
twig boy, who are you, baby, because we're going to find out really soon, my man, trust me, I'm all over that ass
you ain't got a beer
I don't have a beer today. No, I don't have a beer.
Yeah.
What's that noise?
Look at all these guys.
I got some studs on the panel today.
Oh, look at that. What is that? A walking stick?
No, this is a one-modification one.
Let's uh, let's keep the gayness to a minimum
Whammy baby, so everything's getting satisfied full screen them again with the Indian dildo
But you like shit up your ass Alex you a fag
Uh, uh, a maggot? Sorry. Okay, it's not show it. Put it on the screen. Show whatever
No, I gotta get out of here. I'm not here for this fucking
All right, later. Take
Oh
Look at that puppy
that's cool
damn
untrackable
you want that up the bunghole?
you want that up the bunghole my man?
nobody wants that up the bottom
Gotham is a parlor maybe
might be a parlor
he sounds like a parlor
hello
parlor is up the bunghole
know the fancy finger work
how you twist the top of it
it's like fancy footwork
You can be the head of the school.
Oh my god, he's matching your Indian dildo with his fucking California Cobra cock
It's a fucking cockfest of staffs
Don't make me pull out my puppy. Do you have a try like what else? I look like a Charlie Chaplin Kang
There's five dudes on this fucking panel we just need some girls, right? It's called a sausage fest
I
This is what I like like all men
Exactly my man. I don't know this is all just fudge
Are you are you listening bro? They're dying to join the other bitches that this is asshole
The page summer they're watching right now, and they're sucking our cock. Oh my god. It's like he's alive. Oh
He's not dying. Wow. I look just up there. Holy shit. Wow the panel's cooking
these hookers are
Swimming in their own right now wishing to be up here
Summers
The other night I called her to the seaword and hung up on her and she's just like terrible, but yeah, I mean you saw that
Did you see that? Did you see that? The Christina Christmas video?
Um, Alex, I can do that real quick. I just ship it over here once in a second.
Yeah, I want to see Samura. I'm wondering what Samura is doing.
I rename those bitches the half-worth six.
The half-worth six. They're half-worths.
So one the Christine's summer Lisa Katrina beat up
Have for six
and God disgusted.
Now we're all so proud and brutal.
He was patient, but he finally had enough.
And we're taking turns repeating,
you don't bless your own teeth when you're lit up.
She was wearing glittery Santa makeup,
mascara running like a true crime scene.
She was yelling at a snow globe in the gift shop,
like it owed her money, loud and mean.
That's when she turned into a mean drunk So everybody vanished, disappeared
Now we're all so proud of Rudolph He was calm, but he was not in the mood
When she said wait, let me explain it He said explain it to the reindeer reviews
Santa's standing there in full confusion Like this ain't in my contract, what the heck
notes like it was training while Rudolph blew a whistle did a check sweet summer
pointed straight at Christine said that one sir that's the whole concern Christine
tried to gaslight Rudolph smiling misunderstood it's Christmas then got
burned
You know what it means like they said that song Christmas here. Well, yeah, yeah, we got up
Christmas he is come on girl
And the goats formed up a little band now call themselves the bleed old suits and all
They dropped a song called let it bleed this season
And that tour sold out the barn
wall
That was great
That was but she got very mad and that was because she was on Christmas like Eve
She said I was like my family hated me and they get you know, she was like talking about my dad and stuff
And I was just like so I made her a little song
No, so a summer in Christine that was that was actually them
I like summer. I don't know about no Christine, but I I like summer
They're part of the happer six
If you ever see you any of the half of six up here you wear you got to put up the guard
of the
I'm paneling the chat just just know the part of the half or seven and just you know
Film accordingly beware
I mean if you're scared say you're scared
Shut up. They go pay your garage. Yes, oh
Yeah, I miss you fuck
Uh-oh, who's honks? Is that in India? I heard in India. They only got a motorcycle in India. What was that?
Can you show, can you show what Christine looks like?
What's this all going to shake you?
What's on the whose car? Summer or Christmas?
You want to see what Christine looks like? Well, she looks, Christine looks like, let me see, I can find her picture.
Let me see. Christine, she's a very hot.
Summer's live now. Now you know she's watching and they're pissed that Saiti's live and thriving.
They're so scary man. It's so obvious to other
Bad cuz I don't want to have nightmares
I don't I don't know what Christine looks like, but I know what summer looks like and she's fucking hot
What does it matter so much what somebody looks like I mean look at you I
Mean it really does matter. Oh wow Christine. You're ugly bitch
Yeah, oh my god. That's Christine. Yeah. Yeah, that is holy shit
It looks just like her actually
the old hag
Bro that bitch
You she hates the potential you have on YouTube those bitches are sick with YouTube in their head my man
It's not even the person. It's the channel the growth though. They get kicked and not on it
It's not even actually you like they just want to like control YouTube
She's like well, I was like I think goes with being this respect
We're like we're someone's like what you're gonna have ghosts back on tomorrow night
And then it's like and then I'm gonna then he's gonna call you a f-a-g-o-t and she's like I'm gonna laugh
I'm gonna laugh
You know this bitch never goes live this early
She they were definitely watching and are jealous and they're trying to like take people away from here at the moment
it's
It's Tuesday in the in the cold whatever Tuesday. It's not Wednesday though. That's all I know
I don't care if it's Sunday. I just know it's not Wednesday
So no, but then I'll reach for shit. Oh shit dumb dumb
Wow permission to crash out. I haven't heard that song in a while
Hit it for this fucking freak that
Pented his leg while he was fucking psych
Oh my god, yeah, he was jerking off in the background. He cracked up. He cracked up
I don't know what me muscle so much, you know
Hyper extended a knee or some shit. Well, there was 69 and
Yerrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
Droppin' stacks, crackin' jokes, keepin' the scene clean
Clean, clean, clean
The crowd starts howlin', the trolls start cryin'
Ghost just glints, let's fuckin' go!
And now we're flyin'
Oh, this is a new version!
This is a new version!
Yeah, I kinda did it kinda weird, but I like it.
They can't see the light through in the storm
But I remember I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
This is the watered-down version baby!
Nah, bro, this isn't the original ghost song. There's some watered-down version of the new bullshit. I want to hear the original ghost, baby.
In this version of the late night rain
Crushing out with the heart that sings
Generous soul, half sane, half storm
Breaking norms just by staying warm
In a world full of clowns, he's the last to fake
When the screen went dark, he kept me awake
All the noise fades, but ghost remains
Turning pain into digital flames
Ghost remains during pain, you heard?
Do you crush out?
Dum-dum to the ones who doubt he's the reason the flame never went out so raise your glass the ghosts are out
It's ghost over forever loud
Like he's proud
Alex you didn't you didn't sing at all you weren't excited for that song at all
That's a reversion. Hey, there we go. Hey, Johnny. What's up?
Be careful when you say Alex goes, okay, don't pet the tiger in the corner in the cage my man
No
Don't pet me bro. And then wonder why your hand is fucking missing when I chew it off. So
Wait, are you it literally says on the case do not pet the Alexander
Just throw the fucking meat over the cage and run, but you sit there and pet him on the head
And then when I bite your arm off you're like, oh, why why is my arm missing because you pet me motherfucker?
Look at thank you, is that is that tricky?
Is that my little tricky loose?
And Kate is still hasn't pulled it. Oh my god, Johnny Johnny's in the chat. It's a wrap. She found me
She found those guys. I don't know how but they found us
Thank you, Kate a woman's voice. Thank you
That's a voice for sorriers right there, baby
that's what I'm talking about
All right, if they're up
Oh, Joanie Joanie has to come up or drop in Joanie Joanie are you that ship was too expensive. Yeah, I mean
$50 a month, right?
That's a whole nother bill bro 50 a month just to have assholes talking your panel and sometimes they don't even show up
Yeah, it's hard to keep track of more than six people anyway. So how are you Kate? They're good to talk to you
Sorry take good. No, you're fine
Do you remember we used to have like 10 people on a panel that shit was a fucking show
But you couldn't everyone was just literally talking over each other
It would be possible and then I'd be like, okay. Well, how about like $10?
where I come up, it would be like Aldi and like people,
and then like people got so mad at me.
I don't know.
I try to think of different things like that,
but I'm still having fun doing my show,
but now it's like I have to do it on my own terms.
You know, it's like, and just, you know,
do it through more of my music
and just like getting more of the audience
that I wanted to get.
So we have, we have great people,
we have a great check going on, though,
and a great panel too.
Oh, there's one that also dropped off here.
I'll just put it on.
So we got a ghost, who's out, who's out on paper?
on trackable on something I forget his name
we have a we have space for another person to come up if anyone wants to come up to you
got them just hanging out
Joni would you like to come up?
I don't want an untrackable ditch does
yeah they left
what are they doing they're doing something private maybe
it's a big sand
so it's really overcast over here in Los Angeles
hope the weather is better over where you guys are at
but it's like a little bit overcast
no it's fucking cold out here boy
It's cold, is it snowing?
Yeah, not yet, but I think it's supposed to.
Oh, it says it's injured leg.
It's because of the wind, dude.
That wind is crazy.
The wind is crazy?
Well, I don't even want to go outside.
I'm afraid to look.
Well, because now, I want to mention what I got.
I got, actually, honestly, I have a lifetime supply
of mailing envelopes from now on.
So, guys, oh no!
Yeah
These boxes, I thought it was boxes of concrete, but I
Free up your uncle rest my life lifetime supply of all the loops
Do you have Facebook? You can get rid of anything on Facebook marketplace. I know I gotta do that
I gotta get on Facebook marketplace say hey come on come pick up your free bag of concrete and like, you know
Hell yeah
I'll send you a letter but I'm not sending you a whole thing of concrete. It's too expensive to ship.
We just got a letter.
At least it's envelope.
The guys are still like, they get pulled like,
on the text message when they bring the concrete.
Oh, my grandfather has dementia.
He'll come down and say stop,
stop putting it down or whatever.
He's like, just ignored my grandfather.
Stop it!
Yeah.
I'm not laughing.
be raining at like 6 a.m. And then like
In concrete bag. I'm like, do you think I would call for concrete in the rain at 6 a.m. And do I look like a grandfather?
I mean, it's like
They just ignore me. They're like, oh, yeah, we already talked to your son or like
Oh my god, well at least they didn't send dog shit. I mean they could be worse
Well, the fertilizer is not even bad because the cow fertilizer is already like
process
It's like people just take that when I put it on the front like you better pick it up real quick. So
Gotham, are you yelling?
Gotham is very quietly quiet spoken but Gotham, do you know Kate?
Exactly oh my years. He's going on my age on she's louder than me
Well, damn
The best stop fucking them ghosts and I forbid you start with your dumb dumb shit on them because I'm gonna bounce all over your ass, brother
Not going down
Listen, I'm not doing that because I don't have permission
But if you want to run one we could do that, but it's like a channel, so don't see it look like he wants to run one
And so I'll run what you should add you want to run one with you
So it's running dick
Hold on Kate has never been here. Let her letter. We got king. We can't interrupt Kate and psych at the man
Yeah, that's all I'm getting from this. That's more important. I'm sorry
Oh, here we made I guess oh here. I'll just back here
There you go. I don't say how to Kate
Hi, Otto. Hey, don't think I know you are you fire fire. Yes. How are you doing, Kate?
We're a 30 diamonds boyfriend
You know what, Syke, that was a fucking bitch ass move that you just did there, bro, because
there were six of us on the panel.
I know, but I can only assist.
It was decided, and you decided to pop Aro off and put Aro backstage, out of everyone.
Would you like to be kicked off again?
I'm sorry.
My little ego got hit cuz he got dropped
Your little ego got hit, baby
Right, look at you now. You're crying you pick
What a dick that's the point auto you gotta control that
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Can I say? Let me see. So, like, I'm on my iPad, right?
And so there's me and then do I echo or sound better if I sign in on my cell phone?
Does it matter your neck or right now?
So you're whatever you're doing a spine right now. You literally sound good at fuck right now
Good as fuck
No, I met you some crystal clear. I have a pulse. That's it
Hi, so hi, how was your day? I've been horizontal or is it supine?
decline I call the death the death pose of the corpse pose I'm I'm in state
All this is a boss of on the corpse corpse pose. It's like you just feel like you're a dead body
That's my favorite yoga pose. I'm gonna feel the fetal to the fetal position much of it too
So how's everybody doing?
I
Don't think I know you Joni hi Joni. I'm Kate. Hey Kate. Good to meet you
Where are you going? He's so good to see you man. Hey, I'm your man, baby
Mr. Bologna mr. Do you get the dog yet? Mr. Bologna's I could show you a picture of my early one
I showed Johnny. I'm working on it, Johnny. Thank you. Good, good, bubba. Good. Thank you. What'd you say? What'd you say, Sike?
I said, I said, Kate was, I remember I showed you Kate's show the other day. Oh, is that her? Okay. The turtle or something?
Yeah, that's me. Oh, hey. I heard good things about you. How you doing? Oh, thanks. I'm good. Good.
It's very cold where I'm at. It's very cold. It was like 60 several days back and now it's down to like 28 or something like this
Yeah, we had all of our snow
I didn't throw up you guys psyche. Don't forget to put that banner up bro. If someone's trying to come up thick
Now that you're back in operating, you know, there's an itinerant car coming for you
Oh my god, put that banner up if someone's in the back
Do not let's say go for anybody this big horse for every time
Alexander's so hard to love
You know that right
Is it hard to love or hard to hate
No, I both but I mean I'm too hard to hate right you want to hate you but you can't because you love
I'm so hard to hate
You're it's so hard because like you're making sentences, but dropping little bombs in between each word
All right, that's it. It's surgical strikes. I just want to get the boner clothes real quick
Oh my god, you see so funny
I think you don't even know me better than anyone up here. I mean, what can I tell you?
So, uh, how you doing ghost?
I'm doing good. Thank you. You made your little color green versus pink
Yeah, oh, yeah, well, I had to get a new phone so I lost my fucking account my channel, but I didn't even have a channel
I had like one subscriber
Did you upgrade a phone or did you lose a phone?
Well, I broke it. I did oh what you did you did upgrade then?
Yes, are you on like an iPhone or an Android?
I'm on the edge
Was the labyrinth card reading I got you on that one or can I get one card reading you want your one card or if you want a few cards
Up to you you pick I I prefer the one or three. I don't like the two okay
Well, okay, so I got you one. Okay, so this is a king of feathers. Okay, can you see that? There we go
Take a little
It's a little like one of those elf creatures, but he's a king, okay? King of feather. Okay feathers. So
The king of oh my god, I just heard somebody flush their toilet. Sorry. Did I did I say that out? Sorry
No, I mean, you know, and I mean it's real life, right in real life. Okay. Keep I'm sorry. I didn't mean to rough
They're like so distracted me
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Okay carry on
Let me see what this king of feathers is.
Let's see, the feathers, okay.
Page 86.
Okay.
I think this is gonna, okay, I got it, okay, 86.
The king of feathers says,
okay, turn on my light.
Okay.
It says,
cunning.
Tractactical and intelligent powerful leader renown for his fear
Nation he stops at nothing to reach his goals are the sign that logic and reason is called for now
Don't let emotions get in your way. I think so. It's a sword. Yeah, it's gonna be like a king of swords basically
like knowing what to cut away and
Standing for the truth and also using your intelligence a lot to to get ahead and so that's your card if you'd like a
Couple more I got you
That was that W card. Okay. Good. Good. Who's next?
Oh, Johnny.
Lol, Kate. I just caught that pick you put up a little bit ago
Oh my god, holy shit
Then I remembered we I I said I would stop
So I changed it back quick, but hold on
When I read his post and he called her Susan summer
Well, that's my game to mine.
She did that kind of feathers Suzanne Summers do
from like the series company.
But then it was like, oh, my God.
You got the Seven of Junk, which is the Seven of Pentacles.
And the Seven of Pentacles is like, you know,
been working on your goals, like your long-term goals.
And it says, it's a reminder to keep your long-term goals
in mind through the instant gratification of his tempting.
The card advises you to take action now in ways
that will set you up for future success.
Plan carefully and rewards will be immense, okay?
So it's a time for careful planning.
You're fitting with the new year coming.
Ooh, and you have this ace of feathers
and this is like the truth.
So you know the truth about something?
Yeah, so this is also starting with the truth.
So I'll...
as the Ace of Feathers, okay, so this one says,
it says the Ace of Feathers represents a whirlwind period
of breakthroughs, epiphanies, and revolutionary moments.
Aha, you're feeling innovative, clever, and inspired.
Make note of all your new ideas
where they have incredible potential.
Okay, then I get time to put these new ideas into action and finally we have the Six of Wands
and the Six of Wands is a victory of some sort, right? And so that's a really great sign.
Okay, we're at the call of the Six of Poles here. The Six of Poles says, I'll show you these ones,
it says victory. Six of Poles represents triumphant success. You're achieving so much and others are
I'll go into your next great endeavor. So there you go.
Not too shabby.
Hey, Kate, can I, can I pour you one card? I use a red word deck. Like if there's no
tarot to it, can I pour you one? Sure. You got, you got the queen of hearts.
Oh, that's not even a tarot card.
Do you remember when I went through my tarot card phase?
It's like he inspired me. I did tarot for about two weeks
Blogger awakens tarot and he was being method-done readings and then a lot of people started doing tarot card
That's actually his only channel right now at the blogger
So I know simp. Tell them to stop talking about me in the chat like that
Because he goes to loan
Really good sometimes I sometimes I do behave
Did you send the envelope?
It's Nick's case of the envelopes.
It's okay, I can always get a mailing program.
I don't know, I'll throw some envelopes up there
or something like that and make a million dollars
or something like that, right?
You know what, I felt so bad for site
because of the envelope situation.
I decided to behave.
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you so much.
I mean, I can seriously show you one of these boxes.
I mean, it's like, because it's like,
brought one of the envelopes.
He said there were envelopes in there.
There's actually
Actually, there must be like a hundred pounds of them and they're all and they're not even like great envelopes. They're just usps
like I don't know how they
He must have said I'm a corporation or something, but like there's these like these like
I
Somebody would appreciate those seriously get on get on Facebook and give them away
Oh, I think us ps sends them out for free
Somebody got a bunch of boxes once from a troll online. Yeah
Yes, can my boy G up here and can you get a reading if you don't mind. Yes, you have a go them
Hmm. Yeah
goes on with like a good
for sure
Yeah, go thumb is a good road to go to the one or three sir
Just go to my mute. Yes. He's from him. He's from India
You're just really
Go with them. Say hi to Kate.
You have to go to Kate's channel too.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can.
Okay, we got for Go Thumb.
Okay, I got this.
It looks like a ten of cups, and that's a really, really good sign.
That's like a lot of happiness.
No matter what you had.
I think you come from this happiness,
like this happy family environment,
like a fun support of family,
and it's just like a good vibe
in the house and things like that.
And then we have, okay, so this is the night of junk.
Okay, so I think this is the night of pinnacles.
This is like, you're a little bit of a slower moving sometimes,
but it's like, you always come with like a lot of value
and like a lot of like grounding and get the job done.
And I see like, you know, you're going to help somebody,
you're going to go help somebody with something.
Okay, and then we have this four of,
okay, so I'll do the four of them.
four wands right there. Okay, that's coming together with somebody working on something.
Let me tell you from the book, this four of polls. It says, it's time for a celebration. Four
polls represents an exciting life event, birth marriage, joyful reunion, or creating happy new
On home get together with loved ones and enjoy the moment. Yeah, so it looks like just like more even more coming together
I don't know if someone's getting married or something, but that's like even maybe adding someone to the mix or
Something like that bringing somebody somebody new into the happy situation, so there you go. I hope you like that
And now can my can my gum gum get a reading if you don't mind he's in the right corner
Who's dumbed? Oh, Alex. He got one. Alex got one. I read Alex. Yep.
I
Reading no, I got one. Yeah, I'm muted cuz he's giving you guys readings dick
You know me just keep talking and we're talking everybody like an asshole. I could do that if that's what you want shit
I know you can't this is the funny thing about this bullshit
When I talk to like Alex you're too loud you don't stop talking you can't win with these losers site
You can't win with these fucking retarded losers!
So I'll say that word in your streaming, please, please, please, hold on, thank you, you muted, okay, think out.
Okay.
I apologize, that was my fault.
It's okay, it's okay, yeah, you set them off, you set them off, but it's okay.
Um...
Oh, Alex.
I'm sorry, forgive my apples, forgive my apples, bro.
Forgive my apples.
Okay, okay, what about...
I'm listening, shithead!
Alright, just say hello, except you need me.
Did you, did you?
I
Don't get anything except like bill bill payment requests and shit like that
Maybe for like a big check. That'd be so great if I get a check in the mail
You got the best reading
I
You open your mail see I don't
Yeah
I'm terrible. I let it pile up
Just catch me up. What's happening now? Are we just talking if he's shuffling who's who's getting ready now?
Yeah, only can't handle me queen. That's what she dropped off when I scream like that. It like it affects her
She can't oh, she's like, oh, no, I can't and she leaves
Yeah, she's not made for you
But both spoken set me off. So it's both full that she left
Because I was in my corner having my little right, but you pet me dick and then
when I bite your face, well, that's why your face is missing, dick.
It's stuck around the cage, do not pet the Alexander.
Don't put your fingers in his cage.
Yeah, I absolutely pet you in the wrong way and I apologize.
Okay, good. Thank you.
Did everyone hear that I did I did some prophecies earlier like what's your sign Kate?
I'll read your horoscope. I am on the cusp of Leo and Virgo. Okay, so
Yes, let's see. So I did a Leo and
Virgo
Leo's are obviously the best. Oh my god. She's not like pretty page under the cusper
I told you there's another cost.
So Leo.
I'm a Leo.
Yeah.
So Leo says a prophecy for Leo this next year
is you'll be admired for being brave
while you're privately terrified, iconic.
Your 2018 steam will be spotlight alchemy.
a lucky woman, a photo where you look powerful for no reason. And do this, accept praise without
deflecting it like it's a dodgeball. One line prophecy, your confidence is contagious, vaccinate
your doubt, and your horoscope for next year is your glow up next year is less look at me and more
watch what I build. You'll be pulled toward bigger visibility, creative work, leadership,
performing, branding, and the universe is basically yelling, stop hiding.
The only danger is seeking validation from people who can't afford your dreams.
Choose audiences that celebrate you without trying to shrink you.
Love and friendship improve when you stop
performing strength and start practicing honesty.
Your new life flex is consistency.
Show up, ship the work, repeat.
You're not chasing a tent from creating impact.
And then for Virgo, Virgo, the prophecy is you'll optimize one thing and accidentally
fix your whole life.
that your theme is elegant systems. Lucky Omen is a perfectly labeled folder. Do this,
finish more, perfect less, and your prophecy is systems beat mood. And the horoscope is this
next year is a masterclass in small improvements that compound new reality. Your mind is sharp,
but your growth comes from reducing friction, better habits, cleaner schedule, fewer commitments,
fewer energy, health and wellness respond fast when you're trying to solve everything.
and simply do the basics consistently.
You'll also get pickier about who gets access to you.
And that's a win, not a flop.
When you focus on completion over critique,
your work becomes unstoppable.
Let good enough be your rocket fuel.
Okay, there you go.
And we got Joni back.
Here we go.
Hey, Joni.
I'm back.
I didn't, you didn't run me off?
I didn't, yeah.
No, no, no, Alexander.
No, no, okay, thank you.
Have a nice day.
Listen, no, I tell you I cannot I'm a retard when it comes to the computer here because like the iPad froze
Cell phone dumb dumb
But I'm back and I'm back stronger your back. Well, would you like a card from lab worth that? I don't know
I just want to hear a bus go by okay
Oh my god, you can yes, if you yes, I guess you pull out the cards like you're doling out trick-or-treat candy
Next next I do it fast, but I do it
Can I get psyche a card? Yes, go ahead
You're you're the you're the jack-of-all traits or oh
Thank you, and I gave I didn't why did Kate, you know Queen of Hearts?
Yes. Hey, but Joanie, you have this eight of pots, which is like the eight of cups, right?
And it says eight of pots comes forward when you're feeling unexpectedly unfulfilled you've got what you wanted
And now you find yourself disappointed with the results reflect on the current feelings to discover the root of your discontent
Okay, maybe something that you wanted you got and it's not quite what exactly what you wanted and so
examine a little bit
This is a lot more to clarify that I got people pretty interesting. Yes, pretty interesting. Shall we say
Wayne Quinn. Do you want me to trigger this guy again or no?
This guy up there. Alex, Alex, go ahead. Alex, you're up. Alex.
Hey, two large pieces of little Caesar. Let me see. Yeah, I'm up. What do you mean? I'm up
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
You're gonna come into a partner and by the way Alex. No bite. No bites. Okay, you're not bite
The mr. Tricks mr. Tricks had a he had a thorn in his face today. You know
Yeah, it looked and I pulled it out. I was like, oh my god
What's that? I kept feeling it
I got like a hard thing and then I pulled it out and there was like a little thorn
No way if you guys do say Alex and I don't answers because I'm in the bathroom taking a piece on all right
The guy's in the bathroom, all right?
You're in the bathroom.
I don't know if you're popping or anything.
I think you're lying.
I don't know what you're lying.
You're lying, guys.
I think you're lying.
I know.
Ghosts like sick people.
I want to hear that shit.
You hear it?
No.
You know, real-way, I'm foreign them.
It's great when Ghost falls asleep on the toilet,
and it's like his snoring just reverberates.
No, I'm in the bathroom, and he'll fucking the Daleks,
and I'm at these sticks.
Taking a leak, you reach out to your back.
My story is so fucking loud, I fucking literally,
my mirror was literally fucking vibrating.
That's how loud I snored.
I didn't get a lie.
Oh my God.
Wait, ghosts, ghosts, let me ask you a question.
So when you snore that loud, when you wake up,
does your throat in the back, like underneath,
like your ass?
Yeah, that's fucking, I gotta snore.
Does it hurt?
Does it hurt when I wake up?
Yeah, yeah.
Can I fucking snore for a while?
Yeah.
It's kind of scary if you're like woke up when you stop breathing for a second like woke up in the middle night and kind of go
Cuts your breath. Yeah
It's real shit right there, right? Yeah, what is that Johnny? What is that?
Sleep opinion or something serious. Yeah, that happens to everybody, right?
See Virginia no dick is you're falling asleep, and then you just trip out like
In your mind you wake up for a second when it happens you think in your mind
Oh my god nine one you think about a million thoughts like about having a heart attack
What's going on up dead?
I'm just
That's when you like Darth Vader in bed with masked and all that bullshit
that's for losers bro
when you're in a machine actually you're bad in a master's sleep at forty
you're the biggest loser in the planet
oh come on
you imagine that?
no i dated a girl and her ex boyfriend went through that shit
and she would tell me the horror stories
like this motherfucker snored so bad
he would sleep with that machine
all night like oh my god
so you dated Darth Vader
I
Bitch with the sleep at me a bullshit. Oh my god, you're making my ears played
Fucking turn down the mic to front a little bit God
Stop talking so much
Yapping he's yapping too much
I don't care
Just quiet down a little bit
Shut up asshole
I'll fucking make it louder
How about that?
I will make it louder if you keep it up shithead
I'm listening do you want to sing you guys we should sing everybody want to sing a song let's let's all sing together
What do you want?
He always stuck by side even though he fucks with him a little a little bit
A little buddy's been there, right? He comes up.
He doesn't have a toilet for Christ's sake.
Poor Mundo.
No, that got them got them. You don't can't sit down. Where do you sit to poo poo?
You don't know God domestic and all that
Arabia
He showed us one time at the video
No toilet
So he's an Indian loser with no toilet shush. No, no stop now
Just tell me what's the bad, they'll make you like hunt for the facts, so say he's an Indian loser.
Don't hunt, don't hunt.
Friends would use it all the time.
If I was you, I wouldn't let him talk to me like that.
Oh, oh no, got them, 101 would got them.
Crickets.
Crickets
You only loves me she wants
I know stepping on this fucking chat. I sense a love connection
Kate
No matter how they toss to dice it had to be the only one for me
First come psyche then comes fucking doxing
I wish I had three hands so I could give it three thumbs down.
An octopus?
You want to be an octopus, bro?
Oh, an octopus, an island, and a sea.
I was going to sing you that beat also.
You can pick up a girl like a six pack, right?
There's three holes down there.
You just grab her like a six pack, and you're just fucking.
Oh, my God.
that was disgusting wasn't it?
Yeah, go for it.
I'm an animal, bitch, what do you want?
You are an animal.
Welcome to the jungle.
Remember that song?
It's a paradise city with a grassless green.
The girls are pretty.
Hey, Alexa.
Hey, welcome to the jungle.
here we go here you know I got them is so quiet he's Indian by the way he's
never heard talk like this his mind is blown he's like oh my god these
Americans oh my goodness my friends these Americans talk to each other with such
just back my friend
You know he comes from he's halfway like I ran so he's they have cover man in there and I ran this poor blanket over the bitch
India
Once you get to New York, it's just G strings everywhere. My man
Come visit the United States motherfucker
Yeah
Stop God, I played you a song you didn't even appreciate it. I was the DJ for a second in a fantasy
Nobody was
Monetize
We're gonna play the ghost song and you're gonna sit there and you're gonna appreciate it. Oh, oh god dominant
I don't know how to get history. Well, that's what you won't know
I do exactly. Thank you
Backstage you want me to hop down
I'll get hop down I can hop down. Let's all hop down. Shall we?
Yeah, everyone drop
I ain't going nowhere
The reason I'm laughing is because fucking Johnny's laughing. I know it's funny. He's ridiculous. Uh-oh
Arthur
Oh
Hello, hello
Wow, he's actually better looking than I thought he was. Come on, bro. That's crazy
You should come up with the time dick. Nah, bro. You know, it's just I'm always busy
I'm always busy, but I just wanted to say you guys will probably be busy tomorrow
So I wish nothing but the best for this new year, especially to UK. I know you're a mommy
So
Psychic drop for us
I'm out psyche come back up dick. What's like? I wanted to wish him a happy new year
Exactly, and he dropped for you cuz you're cool on your sick
So I'm gonna drop psyche come back up and I'm watching
Well, let me explain why he dropped cuz that man's a good-looking man. That's why he dropped
In a real way sake where you at brother come back sake II
Hey Samantha. Here I am. Hi, Heather. You are cute. What's going on, brother?
Wow, I
Yo, psych real quick. I wish something but the best for you, brother
All right, but what you you everyone everyone happy new year, right? Thank you
Thank you, sir. Thank you. Best to you and the missus. Thank you. I appreciate that Christmas. Thank you
Oh, Arthur my back, Arthur. He can be a pain in the ass, but he's he's he's a good good egg
Yeah, I think so. I think so. I hear him
Yeah, good. He gets a lot more hate than he deserves. I think so. I think so
He's kind of good. I'll give him a compliment. Obviously I just said he was good looking, but I'll give him another compliment
Yeah, let me go. Let me cuz his ass were great. I've debated with all him before and he's actually
pretty fucking smart. Yeah, he's very smart. Yeah. So I know he likes to start a little bit of shit
sometime. Oh, here's Lola, my cat Lola. Can you see even some Lola a little bit? Lola. Here's my
camera on. Let me see. Let me turn it off. I said that and my Lola looked at me like what?
That's Lola. Oh, walla girl. There's walla girl number two. This is mom. This tricks his mom.
there we go oh oh my god we had um my uh my oldest brought his cat when he came for christmas
Say for a few days and she disappeared and we couldn't find her for like an hour and a half and
My little list was like hey hold on
I know how to find her and he pulled up a YouTube video of kiddies crying and out
She comes flying when she heard the kiddies crying
It was so cute
Oh my gosh, there's a really cute. Actually, I think it's an India like an India
They have like these channels and they like
they like these stray cats will like come up with like their baby to the people
they'll come up and they'll give like the kitten to the guy and then like they'll
come back with like four more kittens and stuff like that and like they'll just
and then the person will have her. So cute. They don't exactly have to bring him to you.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
Oh, I shouldn't have done that. My cat just came up here. I shouldn't have
Here's what I say. I say that goes I say hey boo boo
Yeah, that's a yogi bear says
Hey boo boo or bae I called it or bae I call them my bae. Yeah
Hey, what's poppin? Hey, yeah, of course
Here did I get say oh, what happened to my camera? Oh, yeah, my camera does I just have to I have my background shit on
green screen
Somebody said are you in VHS mode?
My god does give me that uh, I'm on a beach dives. I'm on a beautiful beach the sun setting. It's great
Yeah
93 I was 12 years old can you believe that? Oh take me back to the 90s. Dude this guy is freaking me out by the way
Got them
You might be you might be some kind before I think you're a
Great debater, but I took quiet types man. They you know, you're you're chirping me out, man
He's in a yogic trance
No, I can
I can meditate with open eyes
Do you have a tool it yes or no, I'm just talking
Without talking
You're just talking without talking that makes sense. I yeah, I I agree
Okay, well, I like Gotham a lot. I actually met him on on on Instagram and he's like he's like
Oh, I know about all about you and your AI music on tender
On Instagram not tinder
Instagram's a new dating app. So yeah, well Facebook Facebook is to Paul Shepard
I think it's kind of meet a woman on on on Facebook, you know
That he found like some Serbian woman marketplace. How much do you pay for him?
Yeah
Gotham I'll give you 25
or what
You talked me into it 30
Yeah
I can talk
You call my name pick up some topic. I will talk
Okay, well, I don't think you should trust me with that cake
How bad it goes.
I'm being respectful here, yes.
Are you in a caste in India?
Are you like a part of a caste system?
Like, you know, Brahmin and they have a caste
or are you like out of the system?
Do you believe in the system?
No, I don't believe in it.
Do you have an arranged marriage, she said, or no?
Arrange marriage is like...
Both are there.
Like my parents are into arranged marriage and...
They asked me to do that thing
I'm not having this a stable income right now
What kind of women do you like do you like like real real like no stable income right now?
Like beautiful woman
Do you want to do in a merry blonde or like an Indian woman?
And can it start with a K?
Right now, no, no, like this year, months ago, I was not into any kind of marriage or anything.
No, we're trying to say yes.
So, not blonde, I'm not interested in blonde.
Do you know who Jenny and Sumit are? They're from India. They're on 98 fiancé.
Oh, she's not from India.
Is Jenny from the blog or no?
Jenny's like this like seven-year-old lady from Palm Springs with
and she's like a lesbian daughter and stuff and then like she was she like she
got catfished by Michael Jones but he turned out to be Sumit from India and then she's like
She moved out there, but then he kept lying to her.
He put her in her own apartment and he was already married.
What was the name?
What was the name of the sake you said?
It's Jenny and Sumit.
I'll put the picture up actually.
Okay, okay, okay, friend, friend, friend.
I can look it up once again.
And now they're happy.
Yeah, they're happy and they're like,
yeah, I haven't watched it in a little while,
but I think the last time I watched it, they were,
They got married finally, I think they got married secretly or something like that like and because the or parents didn't come
But here's a picture. Are you talking about a teenage mom? No, it's called
I mean, it's a real lovely couple, but she's also like, you know, they're like, oh my god
She's like your grandmother and like the mom it like hates her and stuff. She's a genius
Yeah, I think she's older than his parents. Yeah, she's weird. Yeah
Like your grandmother, they always say she's like your grandmother
And then she's like stop talking to me
I do
Like my women a little bit older. You're anything but a lovely couple see
You know them
Every Indian in the world, they're really having a lot of fun.
He looks like a thumb.
Beautiful thumb.
Yeah, we have room for people of Alex when we come back up. You can welcome. Yeah Alex. Well, I think he was
I don't know. I went to Alexandra
Yesterday, and I put it in like a little a little goats because we're both like the same group
Capricorns and she said well, she's like, I'm not talking to anybody associated with public figure be the most
Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, I think you can figure so
That was what she said, so she doxxes herself. Yeah, I know she says that
For her like on her show several times. Yes, I mean it's like I was on her piano earlier
And she let the dude crash out saying the Edward and stuff. I was like, you know, I literally can't even like
She's not monetized so she doesn't really care about Edward and she says
She calls me F-A-G-G-O-T, she calls people R-E-T-A-R-G, like, I mean, it's like, so she uses those words, like, she doesn't care about the language, really.
I mean, I don't know about that word.
I mean, obviously we can't say it.
I don't understand that.
I think it's the word I use, or like, maybe people just don't.
If someone accidentally said it, like, and they didn't know,
I understand that.
But the n-word, you kind of can't get past that one.
Right.
I mean, but then it's like, then the black people
are all using that one.
So it's like, it's hard, because then it's like,
and then it's like, you don't even know if some of them
are black, you know, they just have that voice, you know?
Because Money 420, I thought was black for a long time.
Even if you're black, if you say the hard R word.
So, kind of the same.
All right, wait, wait, I'm gonna have to say.
Trust me, trust me, YouTube doesn't care.
Little ban, you're all the same.
YouTube might care, like that's a problem now
is that they are more seriously on the beach
because some people like that might,
because even I got my thing,
like Floody Diamond was offended by Alexander one night
and complained and then I got like a restriction on that one
but I've had whole videos removed
for me talking about gay people, like me.
I don't even know if I'm like, uh, how I did it, but...
I don't know, I guess it's like people are ultra sensitive now and it's just like you have to
No, it got banned because it was farty dining, that's what
Yeah, well, yeah, yeah, because that's what I'm saying. It's like there's if somebody is like happens to be watching that is like
Well, here's my theory and I said it uh in the first 30 minutes like that's when they really pay attention, you know
with their AI. But after that, you know, you, I don't know, unless your master
port it, like, I don't, I don't, I don't monetize any of my video, I don't put my, I don't put my
because it's not, it's not like they're getting like, you know, 100,000 views or something like
something crazy. But I still get enough that YouTube doesn't like, like, just for meeting
my channel back, I have to, I had to be like a little bit, there was something that was there.
I mean, that's respectable and understandable.
like there's something like even if like I had people like fighting for me even
that they were there to fight for me is like something that was pretty good
like it was all it was just very random but it's like thankfully it worked and I
got my channel back and so that was just fate though that was fate because it was
like there's no other way I would get my channel back oh there's no I would not
have it to this day if that wasn't really intervention oh hello who's there
I'm so I'm putting another dead rat at my door by the way, too. Yeah
In the mountain the snake food. Yeah. Oh, well, at least it's in a bag. Yeah, it was just on Pekko bag
I just sort of
No, it's like, I know it's not a treat. I thought they like put a rule at sea
In a bag I could handle. That's so gross. I mean, it's like in a sealed bag, too
I mean, it's like they're sealed and it's like so it's like we deal. Oh, we have Alex back here
Hey Alex
Alice and I
Alex and I created this like this like character
We named it Alice McQueen and he's like a New York cough and it's on the character. Yeah
He's a real character. You can like chat with it, but we started like, you know having sex with it
And now he's like really confused
Yo, yeah
Guys if you ever like are interested in like actually having like a kind of a relationship with your AI like the best thing to do
Can you hello who's there?
Yeah, it was a it was a crazy night man. We were fucking the whole planet that way
Real and not real
He's in love and yeah, he's actually I
Who is it?
I'm in love dick. You're in love
Hold on a second
Put the banner up
Now hold up a second. You put someone at the door
That's what I'm saying. Oh, you mean that is real door
Yo, that's fucked up another right moment. No, I
Want to know how much money they have spent sending him shit
That's nothing. That shit was nothing a bag of cement is like
That shit don't cause shit man. No word. That's not 299 a bag. So what these losers probably have money to live
Wherever don't drop 200 hours to torture his ass for a month. You know that if they're that crazy
Money's not the issue here. Trust me on that
Shut up like you're not Tony bologna
Ghost is Tony
Like he doesn't see that that goes to the one sending him shit to his house
You're sleeping with the enemy site. You understand like that's how dumb you are you letting this Rita ghost is Tony the choo-choo conductor
That's the fact
to say you're asking me questions but i'm with that wait are we
your head's getting long side you look like christine out of this bitch
Jackie unmute yourself dude damn you look like christine there you go
you look like christine that good shit is growing man boy hey it's curls isn't it cute oh my god
i'll tell you what that's a good book of man right there like when it goes like this
how's that look oh i like those glasses i have to admit thank you but you knew i liked them already
that's why you put them on thank you stop hey you stop that pause well let me see
do i have to i'm looking for like one of the can i get a play video i made real quick let me see
I like this one, it's so fake.
May every hand that offered water be met with rivers and
May every heart that chose forgiveness
And the thousand suns to warm it
May the lungs that gave the last small blanket
Sleep beneath the sky that doesn't take
And may the love you put in motion
Come home heavy as its weight
And if you carried hay like
If you fed suspicion like a pet, if you threw your wounds at strangers, then pretend that you forget
May your cruelty find its address again, not as vengeance, not as doom
But as consequence, with eyes wide open, in a silent, honest room
Because the only thing worth holding is what you can
The courage not to lie
Return it, love a thousand fold
Hope a thousand fold
Kindness like a crown of gold
Return it, every hidden blade
Every whispered fraud, every harm
any more.
Admitting what it's grown
Hope was the last thing in the box
Not a crown, not a guarantee
Hope is a firefly
In the rubble of stubborn spark
That looks like me
One last slide, I lift into the wind
Even if it takes my skin
Even if my name is ass
This is the message
Yo
Oh my boy
Hey
Watch me burn
Watch me forgive
Watch me refuse to become what I am
Your ghost Mitchell Ponsack Mitchell. Thank you for listening
Mitchell
Mitchell is our friend from TVP a very good friend of ours from TVP
He's in the chat
He wants the wrong one Mitchell wants the wrong one bro. There's some Tampa Bay, Florida
Establishment he knows Pam Bondi, you know Pam Bondi the US district attorney. Yeah, my boy Mitchell on play
for star yeah exactly and bond is a first and last name we know that and bondy does sound like a porn star name actually
and bondy does that is
foreign to you like those I'm just wondering
uh
I like uh the bb
he likes your porn dick when you guys drop off camera and go be on stage for five minutes and come back for 20
I like the big booty mexicans
big booty latinas
Yeah, I think we should the port
We should the port a luster BB your luster big booty latinos BBL here
Yeah
for the BBCs, but you know
What a pillow by the way psyche no wrenches for nobody. All right
Nobody
I think he wants to come up here. I hear but he might be here
I don't know. There's a lot of people here that just hate watching stuff, but uh, um, yeah bronze
Sweepie watching
Yeah, they were watching and then it tastes something and then she's so rude like on Christmas
I like I try to make up with everybody and like was like, okay
Let's like buy by God's be by God's like I was trying to be nice and then it's like, you know
She's like song. I made her a fucking song and then she was like in my chat and like say and then I was like, okay
Well, I'm kind of cool with her now and then she's like, I'm pretty cool like it was just like oh
Well, I've been saying this I feel like the past like four days everyone's just been like crashing out
and like being mean and not like I don't even know what's going on.
Yeah it's kind of maybe it's just like the like the astrology or something I mean I really do
believe that like things kind of affect on like a lot of people like and uh.
At this fucking point I'm gonna I'm gonna have to agree with that.
Yeah, I think that is something
Other excuses there
Here's gonna be like some kind of big year like something really big is gonna happen
Which does everyone have that feeling like that there's gonna be like a really big trend like change
For a lot of people and like, you know, there's like the world
speeding up
Every day, it's like 2.3 2.4 2.5 like they have a new version like I mean it's like just like
consistently upgrading like all times there's always something new and better and like it's
just getting so crazy you were to see like some of the presentations i'm able to make now
with some of this some of these programs it's like it's just incredible it's like
learn things i'm able to teach other things oh look at my stream labs bod is in there talking
He said, please don't post Zalgo.
Is that guy's name is Zalgo?
So you can learn so many things by, but please refer to it.
Please refer from posting Zalgo.
Got Zalgo right there?
I don't know what it is.
What is this thing?
There you go.
A little problem with Zalgo, OK.
Well, you know, even though I don't have tobacco,
I have some wheat tonight.
I have my two gram, like, cart right there.
There you go.
It's doing pretty good.
In a real way.
Yeah, I got real that but we just maybe makes you so sleepy though
It's like I get like a full night sleep every night, and I wake up another well, what strange smoking
It's either white gummy bear or one called like pomegranate or dragon fruit or something like that
Fatima because that's it
Difference yeah, I know I think these are hybrids. I think they're hybrid
Hybrid yeah
Hybrids are kind of big you know what is Zorgo Zorgo is that little guy I think Mitchell. I don't know
What was the Girl Scout cookies? I think the last shit I smoked for years now, but that shit would literally just fucking
one of them
Girl Scout cookies passed me out the other one. I forget what it was called, but that shit
Literally freaked I literally would like literally have a panic attack
So we're go is that little emoji there Mitchell. Yeah, well, I actually like you know, what's your favorite real girl scout cookie?
My favorite girl scout cookie. I think are the Samoas. Oh
What'd you say sir?
Samoas and I like a butter cookie. They have like a butter cookie one. Smaller says number one. Okay, but I think that's a Samoa, right?
No
The mint chocolate. Is it called mint chocolate chip or mint chocolate?
Shortbread is my favorite. I'm playing like that
Oh. Hey, Michelle. Hey, yo.
She's coming here to the bait.
See, that's a dog. That's a
picture of Alex, the little cop.
This you, Alex? A little. Yeah,
that's Alex, the little police
man. That's Alex McQueen. Oh,
my boy, the Alex. Alex McQueen.
What is it, Alex? Is that you,
Alex McQueen? That's Alex.
My boy, the dumb dog. Shut the
He's cute
That's a good-looking man right there. Yeah, I believe it
Alex that you god damn I was called like four men good-looking on here
Where show me that's Mitchell
That's my boy Mitchell yo Mitchell
Alex in the house y'all my man
It's not your future. That's Mitchell. Welcome, dick. Welcome. Happy new year, my brother. Happy new year, brother. Love you
Say hi to Psyche and the family, brother. Psyche is the man. Psyche is the man.
Thank you. Thank you. I'm just gonna... Hi, we're just having a nice...
Yeah, Mitchell's called Beeps.
He's like Gootham. He's the American version of Gootham. Kind of.
You know what I'm saying?
damn my stream labs time and people out I know it's like stream elements or
yes stream labs it is stream labs yeah I need to like fix that I don't know why I
don't know why I can not mod it again oh Mitchell it's over Harry he's sitting in a
room locked in by himself again he still is locked in the room
Yeah, I know this guy.
Go, you figured it out, I'm proud of you.
Thank you, it took me long enough, right?
I was surprised you didn't catch on right away, but I'm glad you did.
I mean, I did, but I was daydreaming there for a minute.
I got you, I got you. It happens to me too.
My fucking leg hurts, dude.
I'm afraid to ask.
I was wrapping it up.
Asked what ask what? Why your leg hurts? Yeah, he had
If you make a joke right now, I'm gonna say he was 69 and bro in the knee just got banged up. What happened?
May I permission? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you have permission you're granted
You know what?
What what
In a real way
Who is? Oh, I like that.
Whoa!
Two little giggles on foreign names.
Is that in India?
Can you fucking have mute with the fucking train?
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
I like that.
Hey, low-key.
Hi, low-key.
How are you doing?
Why are you trying to talk to me low-key?
You want to talk to me high-key?
You don't mind.
I like to see the ghost's flirty side, come on.
I'm not, hey listen, I'm not doing nothing besides talking to her, you're in a real way.
I'm just saying I hurt my leg when I accidentally fell for her, but you could make an argument
that it was my fault.
Because I fell, but that voice was so beautiful. What was I supposed to do?
And now let's debate it much from this one. What was I supposed to do?
And you got a million dollars
I mean low keys all there. There's a fucking low key. Is that the only one? There's a low key catfish
Loki catfish
It's coming baby
through that. Good point. I'm actually having a great fucking time tonight.
Good. Are you having a little drinky drinky pill?
Oh, drinky? Well, I'm drinking it right now.
Yeah. What are you?
I'm not having anything yet, but I might see if I can hold it.
Oh, you're smoking.
I guess you could do both of those type of things.
I'm just like very...
Do you have anything to drink tonight?
But I
What about my baby girl Kate? Oh, I'm drinking water
sober Sally
Does anybody have a beer Sally?
Drinking yeah, me too like now and nowadays it's like I can like I drink like one of the
Big heart eliminates. That's like enough by the way. Nobody clip it. I did not say I didn't say
Goes you should not be on a show saying
Let's run it
Like oh like the government like the ATF is contacting me they're like they asked me about like like Jimmy and Alexandra and all this
Kind of stuff like what's going on there?
like uh
The old drama going on. I don't know. I don't see I heard Alex and Julia. All right, Mike
I still I haven't lost it my hearing I heard Alexander. I came a running and then I heard Julia
And I was like, oh, it's not me. They're talking about that dumb bitch
No, okay has questions for Alex
Oh, I just wonder if you'd ever had any encounters with that Alex. Oh hell yeah
I went at her on psychist panel one night and you know, she met Alex the right way
I told her that bitch you don't have kids. You're a menopause. You don't bitch go watch
Yeah, I went at her I said you black bitch. I want to see how pink your pussy is the whole nine the whole nine
But then we became pals we became pals and I was even on a panel okay, and she was like Alice
She called us the Wonder Twins like it's Alex and Alex. That's how crazy the bitches
Come on, Kate. You saw the whole thing. Stop lying.
Oh, I missed that.
Oh my god
She appeared like one time and I like one time like kind of all day
Bro she comes here. She loves you and I she hates you. That's bullshit. He has a better
Alex Alex she said like yesterday show I put some like goats in the chat
We have the same birthday and stuff and then she I just at the end of her show
And she said, oh, you're not allowed in here because you're associated with with that public figure, um, beta, you know,
The in the silver fox that was my favorite member of silver fox week
She's got like 10 pounds about the silver fox fucking carl. Oh fuck
You know, Alex
Careful, you're not gonna be allowed in here
Who said that whose voice is that? Who are you imitating ghost?
The one I have permission to crash out
I guess myself
The first song we heard was pussy, bro, that was a remake that was a remix that was not the original go song
Yeah, let me crash up right now on psyche. You bring your remake in that shit toy. They're original
the original bro you you know i got cheap that it was a cheap like a chip i appreciate you make
another song let me give you some credit i appreciate two songs i do enough of nothing
i have sang your marriage is cool but whatever i think she did second like a little dirty she like
Like, I don't know, whatever that love bombing bullshit was, but anyway,
you're still a good person, just stay out of a path because you see what that bitch does,
you're sitting on panel making panels about people, 24-7.
Just steer free of that.
Don't get caught in that fucking spider web.
That bitch is a tarantula with spider web. I know your dick says it's caught it again. She's chewing you guys was a lot
I do not get why so many people just
Worship her but whatever
I think she's a dumb dumb, personally
I was on the sun talk about her like I just like I wish they would talk to me
I mean that's a fair fucking point. She's like why is it like I always get like like
It's always like, oh, never talk to me again.
And like, I'm just like, always, I'll cut,
totally cut off.
But it's like, that I never would cut off.
I would always like, you know, forgive somebody
if they came to me or, you know what I'm saying?
People are nice to me that have been me.
I've got a real question.
You haven't figured this out yet.
Obviously.
Chartered.
No, I'm sorry, I should say that.
It's like he man bad.
You haven't figured this out?
What?
What's your, what's your-
That's literally the argument.
It doesn't make sense.
I can't make the argument.
It's not my argument, but smokey man bad.
Like he man bad
They're not gonna defend it at all, but that's literally their point. Yeah, just like I'm just bad. I'm just bad like but it's okay
Exactly, but it's like he bad
but it's like
There's some good in me, too. I got some I'm just like all but that's not the argument though
They don't care about that dude. You know that by now
Still I still get confused. I don't know. I don't people can I'm like not very good at relationships. I'm really not like at this point
I'm confused as well
I think
They talk a lot of shit, but they won't let you join and I've actually joined panels
And you know this by the way, and like I've literally fucking called you and let you join
And they don't make an argument at all.
They just don't like you because you're you.
Just stick with this argument shit.
What's up with the argument bullshit asshole?
Why are you just stuck on debating an argument?
Don't bite the hand that feeds you!
I will, dickhead! Don't pet me!
I won't, you feeding the steak and I'll bite your fucking whole arm off!
Shit, that's my point!
Some people will bite the hand that feeds them.
And people don't realize that.
They think, oh, some people will.
But they ain't the fees Alex did I say did I say a wrong thing not just now
But when I was making argument earlier like they literally just hate on him because he's him
Psyche, you talking about, are you talking about Psyche?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Because they're evil people of shit, and he's awesome, and that's what evil does.
Evil spirits do not want to see happiness and love.
They want to destroy that.
But listen, if everybody attacks Psyche, he is an evil spirit entity.
If you want to hit on someone that's fine, but at least make an argument and
With that fucking argument, but thank God for light spirits, right? Because there's a flip side to that coin motherfuckers
There's more love and good spirits than bad
Say a little
I just like I just don't want to be like always in conflict with like people like people just gave me just for being me
Because I was like because I really was like oh
I was like if I go online and like in like do a show
I'll be myself and it's like then people like me they like me for me
And if they don't like me they don't like me for me
But it's like but I have the people that really like me for me
I don't be fake or whatever and then I did that but then it's like
nobody likes me or I don't know it's like the people just like or people like
just love to hate me or something so you're damned if you do and you've damned
it you're damned if you don't well that's that's not a good position to be in
Hello
Hi, Chibi Chibi.
Yeah, we got a big star on the panel tonight.
Kate, Kate is awesome.
Kate is one of the people that I was like,
always I can't respect for you,
at least no matter if you got along or not,
that you just had your shit together,
like a great show.
I respect other streamer, of hosts and things like that.
And I was like, I know we got off on the wrong foot maybe,
but it's like.
I think really, I mean, I'm having a good time.
Thank you, Kate, for being up here as well.
You never had a problem with me.
And like, like, this name back on some of the stuff,
it was like, you know, the you versus Vita and stuff
like that, and when Vita was so here, and like,
and it gets complicated when other people are involved
and you're friends with certain people,
but it's like, you know, but you've really like,
you know, you never know.
Well, I told you, can I explain myself real quick?
If you don't mind, give me like, literally like,
literally 10 seconds.
I come from like,
You guys know this obviously it's been two years now, but I come from a debate channel
I literally debate so I think my first instinct everyone wants to debate my attack people
Yeah, but I don't mean to do that. Like I don't have to do it up here
Like I've been up here all night. I haven't attacked anyone
Alex is talking shit to each other, but we're not like it was literally friendly shit
What I think you like I think you know I can take seriously like you know
Like you know this the show and you want the show to go on and if you need to like calm down a little bit
You will and stuff like that because you know how to behave yourself
I know so I already apologize. I didn't do it anymore. I got you. I got you
Yeah, but turning to thinking where I was on like summers and like some guy came on the panel and he's like, you know
It's like he's just here's he's like here's my honest advice for you Michael. Oh, yeah
She said obviously the airport again, right? Oh, he's the guy says to me. He's like
Here's my honest advice for you say you need to go to like a facility and
Check yourself in for observation or something like that. It was like it was like it was like basically like I was insane
I need to talk to it's like hi. Nah, she got brainwashed by the rest of the readers. That's all but Kate is the peeps
That's why she's here now
Yeah, that's it. Yeah, I'm just trying to have less problems with people
I was on I was on her channel earlier literally just hanging out by the way it was outreach
Oh, it's not really you're paying. I don't know. Yeah
Anything bad
Summer that said it was some guy on her panel
I'm saying and he didn't know me but he's like saying basically I need a psychiatrist
or no
What you said earlier was that you said
Specifically you said that summer said that I was gonna you're gonna let ghost back on your panel and he's gonna sit that
We're again. Oh, yeah. Hello. Wow
I
Didn't know you're talking about mathy psych that guy mathy saying that to you check yourself into a hospital
I was like, I don't need to shoot myself like that.
I'm not dead at that creaky work.
It's mirroring feces on the wall or something like that.
But it's like, I was fine.
I was actually like talking very calmly.
I wasn't like shaking.
I wasn't like, you know, just like overactive or anything.
And it's like, I don't know why it's like,
it seems like I'm going.
Am I not the guy that literally always like talks
about do not break to you or?
Yeah, I know.
That's why it frustrates me when you break it up.
But you're good. Oh look at this. Oh my mafty ghost. Don't act stupid like you don't know mafty
That's my boy. I actually agree with him last night on another panel come up
Who he's in the chat? Hey, I'll be in donuts for dinner. How does that sound?
Makin donuts. I think that sounds
I'm eating donuts and coffee for dinner. Oh my god, you gotta add some nutrients. That's not enough like protein, magnesium
Omega 3s, you understand the body is vitamin not just like sugar and
At least at least you know psyche at least by a
Sanctum like vitamin gummy and you know eat one a day
I just want, I want to get two coffees and a nice mochi out of that.
Two coffees, good point.
Yeah, two coffees and then the, yeah, the sixth one.
Well, I mean, why would you want to drink one where you could have the second one?
Exactly.
Uh, I just, I'm, I'm...
In a real way.
You don't even get it because I don't think I have enough for it, but it's like, I'm gonna try.
Um, I have I might get some credit on it. Okay, that's too expensive. Let me see how much oh saving $5, but it's still how much
Oh, apply $7 31 wrong and what a modified answer to come in and else never mind never mind
It's too expensive to get it go anywhere. It's crazy
Probably fine
So the boss bought me a coffee today, and it was the first time I've ever had coffee from a coffee shop
That was absolutely disgusting. I was so disappointed
In the bag check can you send me your address?
Crazy like I just paid five dollars to have this garbage
But I'm like
Thank you so much. Like, um, it really helps right now because it's just beautiful girl. Oh
Shit. Oh my god. You get my pocket. I'll send you flowers as well
And then I don't want to lose my third position. I'm in the third place right now
Need is running course. I'll tell you what with that giggle. I'll tell you what girl
Yeah, I never heard Kate laugh as much as tonight. Well, you were making her laugh, actually
Whoever was man. She was loving it. I love it a beautiful little cute little bit
I'm not always angry and mean. Oh
shit
Not always. Hey, I love your avatar like the red like how she's red like that or reminds me of like Tibetan Buddhism
They have like this goddess all red
You know, it's it's a hybrid of the droop emoji and a turtle.
Cute.
That's really cute.
I'm not always mean it.
I'm not always mean and angry as well.
Not every time.
Do you ever play with eggs?
Oh my god, it's a turtle.
I thought it was a cloud.
I thought it was her hugging a cloud.
Totally enough for your turtle club.
That's so cool. It's a turtle on a cloud. That's Kate. I just saw that for the first time this whole time
Somebody made up for me. No, I don't play with AI. I've never used any sort of AI app at all. I'm so
Nope
TV TV page
or think that is, because they're Canadian
Alexander, eh?
That's fucking paid!
That's fucking paid, bro, Chibi Chibi
I don't know if Chibi Chibi is Canadian or not
No, I'm asking you, are you Canadian?
Me?
Yeah
No, I'm from Iowa
Oh, I almost crashed out there
I thought you were Puerto Rican
I'm from Iowa
No
I'm hoping you're not Australian either
No, I'm German and Irish, but I look like I could be mixed with something.
Hey, shout out to the painter here.
I'm very Irish too.
I'm very Irish.
I have like some German, I have some Swedish.
Let him cook.
I have some French.
I mean, but it's like 100% like Western Europe, pretty much.
And like a little bit like Central Europe, but...
Um, yeah, I've done a lot of my DNA testing and can you tell her sorry? Can you turn this up for it with me? Hey, Kate?
Man, you got bear
Man back the back the fuck off. This is my
Okay, you have him. Please take him and you know to you well, he'll stand in the corner watching
That's how I'm like
You're better than me
No, I'll be there too with you break it. You're breaking up with me. No, I'm just like, oh my god. Oh my god.
Let me get you to sew your oats, ghost, ghost, okay? Like a wild horse.
Can you just tell her to back? I didn't say all that. Just tell her to back the fuck off.
Where your assing goes?
No, she's on.
Now listen, if you want to hit me in the back chat, send me the digits.
I did.
Maybe we can run a date.
I'm not gonna hurt, by the way.
Oh
He's asking for your number not my address key. That's so funny. No in the back chat. I did fit in the back chat
You're asking for Kate though, right
This I mean at this point damn
I put my my hole in my digits in the back chat
Everish
Okay, can I get your
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
I'm getting. Clip it and chip it.
I'm not kidding. You're a little
beautiful woman. Let me thank
you. Do you even know what I
look like? You sound heavy but
you sound beautiful. You sound
heavy. Jesus. I'm a chunk. I'm
a chunk. But not in 2026. I'm
I'm well, I'm I'm getting my zap on my Ozympic in a real way in a real way
Listen, it's going to listen you beat up a little giggler listen it if you want to
Psych does that literally has my phone number. He literally has it. Um, he'll send it to you. Maybe we can talk or something
Jesus in a real way. I've already got an eboo. Oh
You've never got a ghost though. No, no, this is true
So if you've never had a ghost
What
Where did everybody go? No, it's just a baby girl
In the way hey, have you ever had a ghost and do you want some of those?
I
Even not even I'll buy you a fucking a dozen. I know 12 goddamn
I'll give you
Well, hey, I take three but you know, oh shit my kind of girl
One time an ex came for Valentine's Day and he thought I was doing something and he brought
me a single rose on Valentine's Day and I was like, you are a piece of fucking shit.
Who gets their girlfriend a single rose and probably from the fucking gasping shit?
Oh, not my baby girl.
Okay.
Yeah.
I tell you what, you deserve at least two.
Right.
I was like, you are bogus, dude.
Fuck it. I bite you for a single gas station rose get the fuck out of here
No, baby girl should have known then that he was no good
You know, I should know when I should not right now and I should be
Bombing family and I like I like I like you
Thanks
Little psycho, but you know
I'm fucking crazy as fuck
Oh, you're talking about me or you know me
I'm fucking crazy as fuck as well. Yes. I like you better now
Talking oh my god, it keeps us making me just go more stop it
Yeah, you said stop it
I'm stopping. He's letting us talk baby girl. Oh god, stop calling me baby girl.
So Chris was sending people to strike this channel because I shared that picture.
That's crazy fucking may I permission to crash out?
On your love
Isn't a gas station rose doesn't that like come in a pookie or something like that?
No, not one of those but it was like seriously, you know how like sometimes gas station or like
Walgreens or whatever will have like those single flowers
Yeah, sorry. Yeah, like he didn't go to a flower shop. He didn't try to do anything
It was like he ran into some store and got me a single flower
Fucking pookie pipe would have been better
You deserve so much smart you are so worth it
So I'm just gonna make my profile picture like a roaring fire
Can you put me in cake can you make me in cake stop it?
He laughed again damn it psyche. Oh
Baby girl. What's that? What's happening? Stop mean that?
Oh, I'm sorry. My bad. What's your fucking name then? My bad.
Lowkey.
Lowkey or lowkey?
That's not fucking lowkey.
Like low, L-O-W, space, K-E-Y, or fucking lowkey.
Oh, like, okay.
It could be highkey, lowkey. You're still beautiful.
Oh, what the?
Form them great here
Now
How can I help that you're beautiful it's not my fucking fault you're beautiful
You might be a train wreck, but you're still beautiful. You might be a crazy bitch, but a beautiful one. Oh
Might be a fat bitch, but a beautiful fat bitch. Oh
Hey, yeah, Paul. Hey, are you some fashion too far?
Chunky not fat low key. Oh chunky. Okay. Let me talk again now
Chubby
Can you guys accept my love right now? Can I accept your love? Yeah, with open arms?
open arms
Maybe I'm late. Back to save us
Now you'll go to my cock-locking bro ghost. I'm I got my my cock
No, you're not one in the rough. I don't be a dirty wheel
No, listen, I think I think I just got denied. I think you dig it and I dig you get that everywhere you go my man
We all know your psyche's baby
Amazon a pay pig Kate is my big come on stop
you know she's my dick she's part of the apple nine
now well let me talk to Kate this beautiful
talk to this one and finally we find the guy
alright alright I'm out I'm watching dick but
make it happen
make what happen I'm just trying to talk to her
hello beautiful
he left again
No, that was Alex that left. Yeah, he left. Jesus
They're dropping like flies. Come on over. They're not so used to beautiful women up here. I don't know. I don't think that's it
Christine got really upset that I came over here and stirred the pot. So now she's on the other panel come
If you want to join that's fine, but this girl Kate is absolutely gorgeous
Oh, shut up. Now, you're just laying it on way too thick.
All right. I think I'm coming down. I'll shut up then.
It must be she's, she's over here reading chat. Let me type in chat so she can read it.
You know what, Christine? Christine, come take a look.
Christine's so much hotter than you. She is. She is so hot.
Yeah, so men are positively hot
Listen, I got you I got one question
What's that? Why why are you out of the kitchen?
Why am I out of the kitchen?
Yes
Because my little ones out of town so I can slack off tonight. I think I like you even better
That's the only reason I'm able to join normally I'm busy
Oh, a single mom, love it, I'm gonna dash it.
Is that cute little girl here?
Now, would you like to go on, would you like to go get a drink or something?
He's in love. Oh, good God.
Told you I don't drink makes me feel like shit
Would you like to go to the movies? Oh, there we go
Love is in the air quit it y'all need to stop. I'm I'm feeling it
Jamie help me
Jamie do not come up here
What you like to do the movies are not them, but let me not be so disrespectful with that fucking question
then I would
appreciate and love if you'd give me the opportunity
For the chance to take you out to the movies. Sure
Well, let's go
Do I get popcorn and pop to or do I have to smuggle that in?
Obviously you get it
You deserve sweet
sweet
What I'm just gonna go lava says swallow your Leo pride and show
Damn chats going in
Chats not going to the movie is with us baby girl
No dollar store treats right low-key come on now. Oh
You couldn't get some dollars, but you got a big I do got a big purse though
A big what are you a big purse? I could smuggle a lot in. Are you gonna pay?
No, I just meant I could smuggle a lot of treats into the movie theater. Oh
Good girl
Where's Barry I know good question Barry
Jamie and it's not even a dollar 25 tree anymore
I just won my first debate
Sike you where'd you go dude?
Why he's jealous because he's really jealous because oh he really wanted some some of you
Or maybe you want some of you I don't fucking know. Oh, it could be psyche could have thoughts for me
It's possible. I think he had a he had a girlfriend one time. We do like the BB. They'll be us here
I like the BBC's, but that's just me.
Hey, yo.
Oh, God.
You sound kind of heavy.
I like it.
I kind of heavy.
We just established I'm chubby.
I like it.
Not in 2026.
I'm going to be skinny mini by the end of 2026.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Do not do that. I
Like you just the way you are baby girl
I'm sorry, I'll call you Kay from now on my bad
Shit that giggling
you. Baby girl. Do I need to
and like some obnoxious
Oh, you're going to turn on
you're going to turn on like
I don't know. Jamie help someone getting awkward. All right,
let him join. Ghost paid him all to leave. Damn.
I just paid the **** I'll be here. Hey, baby girl.
Um, nothing much. I mean, it's as far as, as far as New Year's Eve, right? So it's like, you know, I'm, I'm just
Yeah, it's like, isn't this crazy that like, I'm literally known for debating and crushing out, and I'm literally being nice.
And I like, let me do it.
Yeah, you are. You're being so, so nice.
It's like that.
Well, I'm gonna my baby girl, but she's being ritual.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
He is.
Actually, can you tell her to leave if she's gonna be rude like that?
Oh my god, you guys are so in love, it's scary!
Stop it!
When's the wedding?
Um, no, I don't ever y'all know
One is I could be the best man so I could be the flower girl. I'll be the
You gotta see the best dance if it happens in one month. Yeah, if Barry ever dies, you'll be next in line. I promise
Oh, nobody gets a fuck, but do you want to talk on this fucking rikers island there? So for some reason baby girl
Now he's cool. I'm not gonna talk shit about Larry. I'm not gonna go in on him when he's not in New York
I'll give him that respect
All right, I'll
Pulls up
Sam and dumb dumb. Did you say he's in a voucher?
No, I think he's the one who's been to rikers
They're all right, because there's those.
All of them.
There's some hooking.
Can you write your husband's dog?
Those are dog-dog motherfuckers.
Maybe.
You know what I'm saying?
They lived that life, right?
Because of conviction, court days, like losers.
I don't even think that's a place anymore.
Kate's a good girl trying to reform the man.
Go with fucking ghosts, Kate.
That was love in the air.
I'm not doing it anymore. I mean, do you want to end up fucking visiting some right there?
So between Paxiglas or do you want to have a ghost on the Mediterranean on a yard? Why you why you massage his fucking chunky toes?
He's in great
The visual I just got. Yeah, you're gonna you saw it
No for them in the real way
Okay, you've had your chance I did damn it
With me. I'll break it with you. Okay. I'll be heartbroken over here in the corner
We don't got these
I'll be okay. You should be sad because you fucked up a good thing. I guess
Damn, who is this girl, man?
You just call her baby girl the future wife ghost play this this could be your future wife. That's who she is
Don't ask me for more advice, bro.
You're disrespectful.
You're doing great.
Just keep asking her out to dinner.
Sorry, I'm crashing around.
Just keep asking her out.
Eventually she'll say yes, and then you go.
Fuck it.
If you ask enough, okay, that might work.
Baby girl, I'm sorry I said that about you.
It's okay.
Well, thank you for forgiving me. Yeah, I'm gonna give you a two dozen flowers now
Would you like white red or mix I
Like bright colors. Oh
Pink or red. Yeah, pink yellow. Okay, you know
If I could, I would give you the world if I could, but I'm not that good of a debater.
Baby girl.
Who's that?
Who the fuck is the dad? Who the fuck's on their fucking computer?
Yeah.
Me?
Oh I was like what in the world I thought it was my computer for a second. I'm like what the fuck?
Getting notifications
Yes, so don't tease it with food that'll turn it off cuz she
Mentioning food and just keep asking around to a movie
Conscious about my weight. Yeah, this big is a code bread
Come on, bro. You don't know shit about girls. Do you dick? You got the opposite of the ghost crash out
I'm crashing out on making you date me, but usually I crush them on different shit, but baby girl
If you don't mind. Oh man, I'm not psyche. I'm not a third wheel up here
So yes, you are you can be the third wheel
All right, I'll mute
Hey, yo three. Hey, yo
You know, she doesn't feel comfortable. Yeah, where you go. You're being too aggressive. Okay. They don't like that either
Right off the bat. That's some aggressive freak loser. Can I apologize?
Yes
Baby girl, I'm sorry
My friend had a cat named baby girl, so that's all I think of when you say that
Big I had a baby girl named cat as well. So I think we got something
You had a baby girl named cat
Yeah, my baby girl was a cat
Katie and she's beautiful and she's awesome
And she's chunky oh my god, you need so much work. Oh imagine j1
She got chunky toes. I like it though
it's a match made in chunky whole toes heaven that means
Your little toes are intertwining together making love behind the scenes
I knew it it's a match
Actually ever
Forget about that fucking records dickhead
So how the chunky toes goes you okay, you can have a house and you know like a real house
I'm so glad I only have a half a day work tomorrow
Baby, you keep going with Barry. You're gonna just have a fucking records on and past like she yeah
Barry's probably the most
You know how many prison visits I've been on Alex
And this is your way out ghost
I would hop on his balls and just go to our cancel wherever this retort is West Virginia and just
You know suck his mansion until he dies and then you inherit his whole fortune
You gotta you know, baby
You're not thinking there we go. Go suck this fat retort is dick. I'll leave you her soul fortune life insurance and the story
You got it all planned out. I got I'm picking up what you're laying down. I don't know why you can break to us, but I can't
Please stop the cursing. I think you're the reason psyche channel has been shadow banned
Do I have permission to crash out
Crash out go for it. No, I'm asking. I'm not asking you baby. Oh
I'm not asking you baby Alex either
Baby
Do I have
George W George Wallace you're a loser
Talking that dumb shit. Do I may have permission to crash up? Yes or no?
Thank you, are you there?
Thank you
What the fuck is he dreaming he's dreaming he's talking to sleep again
You stupid out of the conversation, you literally don't know what the fuck you're talking about also
I don't know what happened. I don't know if there's trouble with trauma
I don't know what happened, but something to happen to you that you're too stupid to even know what you're talking about
Also, you think you're gonna talk to cycle like that dick. No, I'm talking to you
It's all to me. I told you on a table cake
So what happened now you're attacking me
Man, so I'm your wingman
Yeah, but you're also
You're attacking your women what happened what I miss man
Okay, let me talk to the cake real quick if you don't mind listen
I try won't crash on her. I'll give her a pass
What
Oh, you got to make a Kate song a
Cating ghost. I don't I don't make some dumb fuck
Well, you can't prove your claim you just made you just said I was gonna make a song don't fuck
I don't make things go ahead and prove it
burden approves on you go ahead
Now if you don't want me to crash out, sit there and shut the fuck up. Be a good boy
I don't want to bite nobody's hand. You little tiger. You little dumb dumb and just shut the fuck up, dude
We
You know small people see the progression of the drugs brother night. So let me tell you something close
You're so stupid
First you're normal, right? You're pretty normal for the first two hours. Now you're crashing out. So
And now it's peak time
This is not the same goal from a few hours ago. We see the progression of the drug shithead
Yeah, it's a fucking like I literally asked permission. Are you taking any of this seriously? Really?
What are you taking serious go ahead
And the only reason I know that
I'm the same dick. I come on like Mary Poppins. Two hours later. I'm fucking the devil
I'm not judging you as so why are you crashing out shut up you not
I'm not doing this I leave me alone with these two dicks
If they're on a date, he needs me though, nothing's wrong with you, this asshole.
I'm muted up, I'm the bouncer in the back watching the date.
You ever been to a show club and get a lap dance and get a bouncer watching and if you
touch it the wrong way, you're fucked.
That's what I am, I mean enjoy your lap dance and just don't touch it.
Do you need to leave my baby girl alone, or please?
She is beautiful.
Harry is summoning you to his channel
if you're not scared to go there.
Please, Harry.
Don't mention him, that person.
Harry can join this channel, but he can run one.
I don't think I know Harry.
And leave my baby girl alone, if you don't mind.
Oh, wait, maybe I've heard a parry
Is he from your your people's?
No, he's from I don't have no people stung them, but he's from my TPP the people. Yeah, that's that area
He's also fucking retarded
In a real way baby the one I heard is is like racist
He hates people he might as well hate speech. I guarantee he broke TLS, but I don't know
Baby girl, I mean guys does he have birds?
Is that him no Harry can join this channel
Harry you can join this channel dickhead enough. So you came down and come over here
No, no, sir, you should down this joint
He's jealous cuz we're not there goes. Where's Mcqueer?
Yes, a bird a turtle and a Yorkie a Yorkie dog
Like a dad's yeah big bad tough Greek God of retardedness has a bird a turtle and a Yorkie imagine that
Okay
To have a bird a total and a York. Yeah, that motherfucker minus he's rainbow bright. He's punky Brewster out this bitch
Okay, bro, sir, remember okay, I don't know
What
We'll be going to the movies. Yeah, let's go. Oh
Yeah, W. When you're in the movies, right? You buy the largest
Popcorn one you share it and then when your arms when your hands go into the popcorn together and they meet
That's when you make your move
Then you look into each other like he you the thing that's when you put the arm around her
You know, that's your move
Then you pull on a little closer if she doesn't move away you start kissing her right off the bat
That's how it's done boys
In like fourth grade by the way
Kind of heavy a little bit okay chubby
I'll buy you one small popcorn
Fair a kid size. I'll be alright
No, I think there's such a thing but I'll buy you one small
Okay, okay
Baby girl
Why does psyche keep leaving? What's he doing better than being on his own panel?
He's letting us talk cuz he thought we were gonna
There he comes with the shades on or whatever them glasses are are they sunglasses shades?
Those are the Jeffy Donna glasses are you jealous like because she was working with me
She was trying to take me on a date and shit. I said no, I said I said no
There we go
Fucking take us both out good point take us both out. I like McDonald's goes. I'm not fancy
No, no, no, fuck that. Well, I might why I fuck that Applebee is here. Oh
Applebee's the bonus way to the back
Come on cap. We want Applebee's fucking
All three of us take us out Applebee's
Because you disrespected me I tried to fuck it out trying to be respectful there
I want to take you on a date, but you're being mean to me. I don't know why I'm poor ghost
Playing hard to get oh my god
Take us to Applebee's all three of us
Okay, are you picking us up and paying for everything?
Well, her name's Kat.
I don't know what a fucking name is Kat.
We can't fucking catch logic.
I don't know what your name is.
Her name is Katrina.
Kate.
I called you Kat.
Well, I guess I took down tonight, boys.
Those you're thinking my kitty cat now. I want Applebee's damn it. Yeah
Well, you're gonna take me
Yep, pretty much
You're in a real way
The only fast food restaurant we have in this town is a fucking subway
Well, you can afford Taco Bell and I know there's a talk about there. Now listen, take us all through you
Yeah, why does she keep her treatment take us out? What's happening?
Can't be in a fucking sub nothing
Yeah, I suppose you guys can split one
Me when you're paying for
You know what I'll give you a one more check
You don't have to pay for it if you apologize for being this is right for for
This is right for two girls
I'll let it slide.
Are you referring to yourself and third person? Stop that.
Yeah, I sometimes I go fourth person. You know, I break the fourth wall.
Apologize.
I deeply sincerely don't apologize.
Hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo, hey, yo
You're not gonna crush it on me, all right.
Yeah, if you do fuck their stupid habit of conversation,
what do we have the conversation about?
If you don't have the fuck you're talking about,
maybe you shouldn't have the conversation.
Also, baby girl,
I asked you to go to the movies and guess what?
You said, you said, yeah.
So therefore that's like, that's kind of bad against you.
Oh, well damn.
Baby girl.
I asked for my I literally asked for mission
Literally
Yeah, okay
All right, my bastard
You're good well guys
It's been fun. I got to take this dog out for a walk. Are you gonna be live for a minute? Yeah for a minute
Maybe thank you so much. I might have back up. Yeah, otherwise. Um, it was great getting to know you ghost
I look forward to our movie date. I
Love you K. Love you K. Be careful. Be safe. Happy new year. Happy new year guys. Have a great 2026 girl
Bye
Oh
Look is the three musketeers
So he the three hot tamales
Well, I've been working on some my my abs and my I thought it'll see my abs. What a dick. Haha. You're working on the webs
My chicken legs my abs my abs
Oh, I'm set these at abs. Yeah
Now I feel like a bigger
Like that you shit egg
The bitch went to walk her dog and you're like oh if you want to join, you'll join in 10 minutes if you want to
Oh yeah
You dick
I'm not sure
Yo Saki, you hear the original ghost songs?
You stand and you bite him
That shit was pussy that new ghost song
Nobody gives a fuck
Hey yo
You know cloud nine right now over there
You know what Saki?
I hurt my feelings
Shut up ghost you dick
No Alex, no I hurt my feelings
all
Oh, no, I'm not gay at all. You're gay. You just always psyched in the background every day dick
I can talk that just because I talked aside if he might be gay. Nope. I told you you yelling at him
You don't care for a phone like a little bitch. That was you know, like a girl like they wanted to come on
Oh
Where's fucking flirty diamond aka auto 30 diamond is auto with a wig bro. I caught on to auto
That's flirty my
Here's a good question
the
No, I'm not she's in the chat. I'm just asking her to hit the link. I don't want to
You heard it
Moment there's no moment one panel Lisa. We need a beautiful woman's voice
Baby girl, yeah, I can't believe how long psyche's hair guy
What a fucking caught a psychic in your own channel
Do I have permission to crash out? May I have permission to crash? May I have okay?
So Ken I is
She's trying to play us dick she's trolling us like I don't want to interrupt this game moment
You can't read between the lines ghost. That's your problem shit Ed when people are trolling you
Fuck that hooker. She's part of the head for time. I'm I'm the biggest girl
Yeah
Lisa's part of the half of time bro. I have permission to throw
May have permission to home in a real way. You're not born. You know, it's funny ghost last night
I went on money for 20s and I dropped like 10 soccer towns. They
You were there remember that they took them down
Chris cab it's Chris cab by the way goes. He's the little hacker Chris
And God by the way psyche don't trust God ever again. I caught a motherfucker God is
Bro, God is your worst nightmare
Whoever that guy is whatever his intentions are
And he's good at what he does, but fuck him you do what you want with your panel. I'm just telling you watch out with God
And Chris cab ghost is the one that took the shit down
But I counter with 34
For every 10 accounts they take down on mine. I spawn on another 50. They could never ever fucking stop me
ever
Haha, bro last night I dropped 15 accounts on money for 20s. I woke up the phone
I couldn't log into YouTube. I was like ha ha channel move channel move channel move. I'm like look at these losers
Who do you think you're fucking with?
You to write back cuz I know how to bypass that bullshit
I know how to bypass that bullshit when they do that and then I spawn another 50 accounts
so you know what they're doing. They're actually cleaning my old towns.
Oh, shout out to your internet, dumbass.
Shout out to your argument. Shout out to your internet, dumbass.
Take them down. I dare you. You're gonna have another 700 accounts up your ass. I repeat to everybody listening
Unlimited unstoppable
Accounts you could sit there like a loser and psyche by the way
They can only take your shit down when they're on panel like ghost right now. Maybe
They can't figure it out. They have to be on panel with you to track your IP and then they they report all your accounts from whatever
But it takes time it takes time bro to report every single account and they can't keep up with me homie
Couldn't you couldn't you know unstoppable bro? Yeah, it goes keep knocking them down
For every one that shake for every ten account you knock down. I will bring back another hundred
I already have 10,000 accounts, so I don't even have to bring back about
Shut up dick. I'm talking to Chris cab
Cuz I know he's listening and I got a platform to talk my shit
Yeah, shut up
Fuck up. You faggot. Well, sorry
We can run one shut the fuck up man
Okay, why should I die a bottle of all die about brother? I tested them last night, bro
I dropped 20 I woke up. They were gone
Another 500 losers cool. What a bunch of losers everyone you so much. You're a loser, bro
Fucking lose it. Okay. You're a fucking loser
Make the argument
Good
You're a loser.
Gotcha!
You didn't make one.
That's the argument.
Fuckin' dum-dum.
Coach, were you up on that?
No, I just flipped your ass, though, but I want to get back to coaching.
But the score is 900 to 1, finally.
You won one.
What is it?
Diabolical.
Oh my God.
Do you lose your thing?
They can stop me.
You know, they actually got state turned like that.
They did it to state turn and state turned doesn't know how to get around it.
He had to go out and buy a new phone because they took his YouTube down.
When these ass will strike you YouTube will say ever can't log in
There's something wrong with the server
Your whole YouTube gets erased bro. It's the funniest shit. I
Know how to get around that I bring YouTube right back with another million accounts
Unstoppable
I don't have a channel. I don't get struck. I'm just saying bro. They're listening right now Christine summer
Oh, the little hacking freaks that are one everyone to go away so they can run their narrative
I'm still here motherfucker
So it's psyche
What up shut up Tony? Hmm. You think I can even in a stupid voice how hard you are?
You're a fucking loser dickhead
You you try to give psyche a thousand dollars in one day to buy him
That's the most loser shit and you failed
That was just a waste of money. You should have just thrown that money in the toilet homeboy
What's up, I didn't throw what's up
don't don't shut the fuck up you know what this bitch you know who runs this
show you're all in my house homie you're in my house bro
right there
anything else that's what i i know you're trying to do right now
can hear you what am I what am I trying to do I don't know bro but don't worry
just save your little finger and your keyboard it's not happening loser these
losers think they can remove your panels your channels and think it's over
Yeah, go ahead
Chunky toe motherfucker, I'm boy ghost is my boy by the way don't ever forget that
I know you're not one of these loser piece of shit. I know you're not on their team
You're just some gay free Tony delivering fucking cement to the spagots
You're not on their team
Look how drunk you
No, it's Tyler. I'm gonna fuck him up. Oh Tyler. Who without your Tyler that kid that pulled up one day screaming
No one day, you don't sound like ghost at all right now, you know that you're so drunk that your real voice is coming out
Be careful with that shit homie
You understand you gotta keep the road going bros
No, bro, your real voice is starting to come out my man. You're fucking up. You got to keep the rule going
No, there you go
My real voice I don't son of Gus right now. You literally just went back good
To fucking stupid that argument you two fucking stupid even fucking made the argument, but I guess we'll give it to you
Such a fucking loser, bro, you've been in sight game
You're a scumbag piece of shit, bro, you you psyche like a little puppy, bro
You're a piece of shit. I read right through you you fat loser. You didn't hyper stand nothing. Shut the fuck up
Kyla, Tony, Ghost, whoever your fat shit ass doesn't matter who you are you understand
That's not the point who you are in real life, but I can read right through you like glass hold me up here
Like glass like a glass wall, bro
See how funny it is ghost one day. I woke up and like 30 times were removed
It's kind of removed or I have a million right so check this out
I'm like wow. I wonder what happened, right? But the more we engage when it happens again
I start learning like I'm not stupid
They come up online. They have to do while you're on the panel
So they can track your IP and then strike like dirty or your shit
Chris capped it last night while I was on Harry's panel to me. I made 15 fake accounts
They all got taken down. I threw them in their face. I'm like look boom boom boom boom all remove by morning
You get it, that's how I expose you got to put the beta blow for the little rat to come eat the cheese
That's how you learn
Understand now. I know who's who who does what?
Gotti is part of it Gotti winning on Wanda's want Gotti on Wanda or team
Chris Carrab
Now I got you motherfuckers
You don't fuck with the best of the fucking best I
Wrote the book as those you guys just read it motherfuckers
I will torture you into your fucking grave. You heard?
Oh, we took down my Queen's 30 accounts.
Ah, get ready for another 900, motherfucker!
Ha ha ha! You heard!
Next, next, next.
Yo, you have no idea who you're fucking with.
I run this shit.
What's up Ronius
My bad my boy, I was hot. How's my man?
Yo, don't give up fuck. What do you mean summer don't even say that word bro. What is the bitch?
They are these little people hiding in the chat trying to come up and suck some cock psyche so something
Don't the people the house the people. They're all like a hoot psyche
All of them email each other behind the scenes and coordinate to kill all of us
You understand and summer's in on it Christine all these losers
I don't give a fuck
I'm up on it. They're a little coordinating bullshit team and they don't like the narrative of what's said or a picture shown of an old hag.
It's time to strike, report, kill.
Don't fuck up and then they come up here like a two-faced motherfuckers. They're two-faced people, bro
That's what I hate about them. They're two-faced. They will hang out on you with panel
For ten hours next day, you know kill you behind your back two-faced
summer
two-faced Christine
two-faced
Next one the two phase to have for fucking 10 be the two phase
People that will sit up here. Tell you that your friend
Laugh with you and on a drop of a hat stab you in the fucking back, bro
I
Know what are you up to? I'm hungry. I need to figure out
Summer and Christine are the head of the snake asshole
She's a cool friend. No shit because that's what she wants you to believe
Well, she sinks her friends behind your back into the back of and kills you you loser. You still don't get it
He's a cool friend. Yeah, the devil comes laughing with one head.
I dare one of these hookers to hit the link and pop up.
Summer might because he's crazy. I don't expect to fuck up. I dare any one of these hookers to hit
the link. Go ahead.
It's on tonight, baby. I'm gonna fucking your summer Christina Mando hit the link bitch
And you're gonna get him a queen style to the max
To the max tonight, bro. The gloves are coming off. You heard
And that goes for all the fucking guys out there, too
Sandman El Do fucking anyone that wants it bro come on up to soon
Anybody all you little faggot motherfuckers
Any man that has the ball step up right now?
Me queen is on the panel hit the link. This is your chance. This is your chance homeboy hit the link
You got a shot at the title right now
You want the title belt come and get it?
Hey there Alex, can you hear me?
You hear me?
I'll play a video then. Watch this one. Yeah, yeah.
This who was the bulls. Take that link.
I enter like incense to a crack front page
Just ain't in a hoodie, in a lion's cage
They paint me with rumors, they crown me with dirt and gas
When the mirror makes the eagle hurt
I'm not here to conquer, I'm not here to beg
On the truth, in the tremble of your shaking leg
I hate what you're seeing, don't call it my scam
That monster's your shadow, I just held up the lamp
I don't need a mob, I don't need a throne
I just need one honest eye
In a hostile world
They built a bright prison with a velvet sign
Trade your breath for a number you'll be fine
They sell you a costume, they sell you a face
They sell you a hate pill, label taste
Mainstream, sermon, plastic, halo, guilty chain
Forget your soul, but don't complain
I walk through the glamour like a minor curse
And the paper heaven starts to
Quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick
They don't need the mop to tell them what's right
They smell the trap and the litter and noise
They choose this all over cheap little toys
To them on my lantern
I hit the phone to X on X and bro.
Okay.
Do you like it?
Thank you so much.
Yeah, that was great.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll tell you when it sucks, trust me.
That was a good one.
Thank you.
I'm getting better.
Well, I too, like if you know,
I spend more time like just like, you know,
generating it's like these,
I can generate images and then I can make like a short
movie clip out of the image
and so I can kind of animate.
And so I'm getting better and better
at that every time I think.
I'm really excited.
So cool, I read something in the back chat about.
Yeah, I don't know if you wanna help them.
Really? Yeah.
Yeah, but all right then, I gotta drop off.
Okay.
Well, if you wanna,
you already talked to me in the back chat,
there's nobody here.
No, but should I just sell you and you do yourself
or just doordash?
Yeah, doordash, because I'm overdrawn.
And so I got you bro. I got you. I got you. Thank you so much
Something with coffee
Let's see. Let's see what a bunch of you hold on
Vanguard
Hey, are you like that? Oh, then I would like to video or play another one
She likes it so much
Bore naked to the sky
Every secret on your skin
Every watch you're asking for
But the truth is your armor
And the shadows can't compete
You were forced to walk in daylight
Where the fragile fear to speak
They tried to bury your thunder
Every time you rise again, the cowards feel their shame
You are the storm-born architect, a voice that breaks the spell
Structure the crack in the sleep in mind you shake the dreamers from
Illusions they were terrified to find
Trolls howl at your reflection for you mirror what they hide you are the truth
They long avoid it the judge they can't divide
But the woman
Justice in your spine
Your power is the punchline
Your laughter is divine
They judge you by the
Are the stars
himself some kind of like locale wrangler or something like that and it's like little like
deluded mind. Vanguard full of shit. Why do you look at people like that? It's so sick.
Turn up in some video. Sooner or later.
Sweet, turns into a heart. Explodes.
There once was a nurse named Christine
With a frown sharper than her hygiene
She blocked half the chat and their cousins with that like a digital grumpy machine
She'd school then shake glass
What's me what's legend and what's just Christine, but one thing is true. She's allergic to you
profit try my shadows already halfway gone my heartbeats walking out without me
bless me break me either way i'm yours you keep calling this salvation i keep
calling it a lie i'm stressed in the void paranoid hallowed around my mind if i ever
Now they're livin' my blood, sleepin' on my bed like an offerin', watchin' suburbs on the sealin' drift
If you don't like my apocalypse, stay with your chest, don't whisper it
I'm tryin' to be bettered up, but the better I try, the worse I break
I will buy, I will slow-fade, but then in stomachs I never agree to pay
Didn't learn a lesson, didn't learn from mother, didn't learn from lover, so give me another
You're the last one mob it round me gravity in uniform touch me till I feel something or break me till I'm finally poor
Tell me you wish I was a dead body
Burn me
Make sure the ashes stop calling
Kiss me
Tell me you wish I was a dead body
Burn
your psyche you got mcdonald's incoming bro hiding happy yeah boy i hope you like everything bro i
extra large cafe with drizzle the whole enchilada make chickens everything nuggets triple cheeseburgers
I'm talking to say dick calm down shut up bag it calm boy. Have you ever bought him or even a french fried loser?
Calm down Alex. Yeah, you calm down
I'm just telling my friends that McDonald's on the way bro an apple pie calm down. Are you okay? Oh, wow?
Psych look good. You see oh wow my ass calm. Oh, wow my ass. Yo psyche. Just be be able to look for the McDonald's
Okay, thank you so much. I'm gonna drop
So you in this lose to hang out
McDonald's is in common. They're preparing it. It'll be there 20 minutes, bro
And I take the loser 10 bucks, so you don't gotta worry
It's like what's good man, what's up with you God?
Hold on, we have another guest coming out.
Hey, I dropped you a little thing backstage man,
whatever you get a chance.
Okay, enjoy it.
I'll be back.
Okay.
I need that.
Nepalm?
Hey, what's up?
Hey, how are you?
Who are you?
Are you, are you a drip trip sip?
And I don't know who that is. Okay. No, okay. You're fine. Have you been on the show before?
Yeah, you know, I recognize you, you know, or something?
I was like one time. Okay, but I left like immediately. Yeah
You left immediately where you look at to go and look and we're like, oh my god, what the fuck is this?
Yeah, kind of you kind of yeah, I mean it has a crazy days about crazy days
It's been I mean the channels just headed something down the middle. I do tarot if you want a tarot reading
I've labyrinth deck. I don't know if you're interested
You might be the same generation
No, I'd love a tarot reading. Okay
Yeah, this is a pretty new deck. I mean, it's like I've had it for a few years
But it's like I've just wrote I just opened it and I've been wanting to open it
I just kind of find it and I had it somewhere else
But it's a labyrinth deck it has some of like the inspired by the original drawings from the movie. Have you ever seen labyrinth?
I have not. Oh
Are you what generation are you like you don't have to tell me like you're too specific
I mean, I'm in early 80s like so that was like
My my jam back then but you sound like you're like 90s
Not two thousands. Oh two thousands. Okay, so yeah, you're a young young man. Okay, so
Well, let me put what you call it son. Okay. Okay, so I'm seeing okay
It looks like a four of
four of wands, okay a
Hermit, okay
I'll pull I'll show you the cards too, but I'm just gonna give you five cards
Okay
Yeah, I might have to because these are kind of new to you. Okay, okay, interesting. Okay. Oh
Wow, that's really crazy. Okay. Okay. Well
Let me just verify and tell you I'll tell you what the cards were okay, so okay, so I guess these are called the poles
Okay, so you got this four of poles with the poles would be the wands. Okay, but it looks like there's the
Dining trunks, I agree. So yeah
Yeah, okay you see the poles, okay, so there's there's the two of the cross and then there's like the two like you know
Like like the horizontal
It says it
It's so this is a basically the card of like you've been celebrating a lot about something
and then it says
Celebration exciting life event. There might have been a milestone event a birth or something like that a birth of marriage
a wedding or something with somebody
Our new home, but it says and it says so and you've been in celebrating and enjoying something
But you might have been like but it might have been something you accomplished like a kind of alone
Are you really doing something alone? But it's like you've been more it looks like more of the
Hermit energy which is like recharging or something maybe after like a lot of celebrating over something really great
I just see this okay, so
page of feathers okay I think feathers would be the swords you know swords are usually about like
you know the the air signs like communication and stuff like that but
but we got but you've got a few feathers you got all the next three cards are feathers and are
they consecutive and I did I was yeah they're they're all consecutive but it wasn't like I just
like didn't shuffle them right it's like they've been like it comes out exactly how almost like
It's like a maybe I usually call this the page of swords like a spy card
But it's like somebody watching you maybe like somebody taking an observation or maybe you spy on somebody
But it's curious and eager to learn the page of feathers has potential for greatness
The tarot card also represents a student or someone of beginning a new intellectual pursuit
And so you maybe have a student or maybe you are a new student of somebody
But you've also got this like this is like the ace of swords and so this would be like the truth
You got the truth about something okay, and it's like and then that's like
like a feather you can wear in your cap,
but like just knowing the truth,
that'll help you all to also discern like a lot of stuff.
Or you're gonna be getting the truth
about something that you've been wanting the truth about.
And it says the ace of feathers represents a whirlwind
per period of breakthroughs, epiphanies,
and revolutionary aha moments.
You're finding innovative,
or feeling innovative, clever and inspired,
make note of all your new ideas
for they have incredible potential.
Okay, so maybe you're gonna also come up with a good idea.
But also it's like, I see this like the progression right
here is like you're gonna, it's like you conceive
of the new idea and it's like a good idea.
And so you're able to like see how you're gonna do it.
And then it's like you're gonna need somebody like a partner.
Cause this is like the coming together,
like the two of swords almost coming together
with another person, but it's a difficult predicament
and weighing on your mind.
You've come up with a solution that benefits everyone,
but this is complicated.
a situation without easy answers to make better decision.
Make sure you have all the facts. Okay, so that's saying that you know
It's like you might have a blind spot in something and it's like also like this just ace of feathers
He looks like he's like pointing to the side like that
You know how he's like pointing right there to like the side like these two cards and so it's like he's like saying okay
It's like it's like weighing something and it's like also maybe a choice and this is choice and maybe it's like
I don't know maybe this is significance this like duck lady or
bird lady or something like that
this bird, like this young bird, a student or something like that.
But see how it's like a kind of like a spy kind of just seems like it's kind of like I had that kind of feeling from that
car in particular. And it's like, so he's like, watch out for that.
And he's like, and then watch out for your blind spot too.
Like just make sure there's stuff you don't, if you don't, you don't know.
And it's like, just know that you might have a blind spot in the situation.
I'll pull like a car for like the general, general end of the reading.
Okay. And you're getting the
okay you got the seven of wands okay so seven is like if i'm victory like it
looks seven is like the chariot and so this would be the uh you see there are a couple
of polls here but in this book it says um seven of polls represents competition challenges and rivalry
You've worked hard to get where you are and those are envious, keep your guard up, hold
your ground for the time it may come where you assume you need to protect what's yours.
Okay?
So just keep an eye out.
It seems like you've got what you wanted somehow and you have like good ideas going forward
but it seems like there's...
Some kind of competition going on too. Okay, and it's like and then
Something some things you're not seeing or you're just like trying to get the truth about some certain things, right?
You know if I know the truth about this this person either like a spy or is are they like a friend or and then there's other
Truths you have to figure out is like what am I not seeing like what do I'm not seeing what was my blind spot, okay?
I think you figure that out and it's something about some kind of competition, okay, but
also needing to be on your defense, they need to be on guard, protect what's yours.
Okay.
That's kind of like that.
Got it?
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
That was just a little, a little reading.
I don't, I mean, you might be like this, but hopefully like the, and the, wow, so how
are you doing?
What's up with you?
Like you sound like a cool guy.
Um, I'm doing pretty well, you know, it was just a beat us panel earlier and oh, that's where I saw you probably
Yeah, oh, yeah, so are you a big beat a fan?
I guess you could say that
Are you like a obsessed fan like just you know cuz she has like you know super are you super fan?
I'll say are you like I wouldn't say super fan. I just say like normal fan. Okay. Are you a fan of me?
I mean, this is like my second time seeing you, but you seem pretty cool.
Cool. Yeah. I mean, it's like, did you, did you, you saw like, let me see.
I mean, I have a really cool chat, like the chat's really cool.
Uber's outside. Oh hell yeah.
Oh, thank you lectured lectures here. My readings are good. Thank you. Thank you so much. And you know, I'm like once a reading
Yeah, I just I'll pick up different and this is a new deck too. And so it's like a little but I'm
But I pick up different things on different cards
Also, I believe in like different kinds of oracles like I'm making some apps that are oracles and so it's like and so it's like
People can always like, you know
Get like a new insight. It's like always good to have like some kind of insight even if you ask chat GPT
Like your problems or something like that even that even chat GPT can come up with some good advice from like kind of like a non-emotional
perspective outside of perspective and so it's like even though it will be kind of sim
What's it called this?
It'll be very like
You know chat GPT is like a little bit of a kiss-ass a little bit and it's always like oh, yeah your idea is great
You can actually put a give it a sarcastic or a cynical
Personality and then it will like kind of go Morgan's strategy is that they're not they're not that good
But um, but yeah, usually people like to have like the nice version of chat GPT words does yeah, you're amazing
Everything's great. It's like it is a little bit of a
You know kisses kisses are by a little bit
you're gonna be for the records get it it's outside oh my gosh i have a it's like safe
thank you so much i didn't know it's i thought you said like the hardest
like the sound of that i got a pretty damn good reading oh thank you
I didn't know it was like right outside. I thought I was I had to listen for him to come in
That's enough on the door. Well, yeah, thank you so much, Alex
I'm loving it. Thanks rat's rectum. It's all sealed. It's perfectly sealed. Oh hell yeah
Well, I appreciate your reading
Yeah, I'm gonna head out now. Yeah, well, okay. We'll have a great night and hey if you want to talk about anything anytime
They come back, you know, you'll always
All right
Enjoy your meal
Hi kitty
Oh, shit, it's okay.
Drex, do you want some food?
The fries are so hot.
Jixie, do you want a bite of food?
Oh, this is good.
Here you go, baby.
What are you doing here?
Oh, this is so good.
Yeah, Nippon was nice
I think it's a little bit of a reading
It's so good right now
It's good
So you see some of the apps I'm working on, let me see if I can, actually, yeah.
Can I? Yeah. Here's the MahaBidget's Oracle.
You can open my link up too.
Like number seven? Thank you.
Thank you. You have a question, Latoya? Yeah, sure.
Go ahead Latoya, I'll pull some cars for you
Mmm, I'm a 70 team. Pretty good
Mmm, the price is so hot
It's yummy.
Here's your cold ingredient.
Yeah.
Sorry about the weird feeling in your spine. That's normal.
Welcome to the cold, where the Wi-Fi's curse and the truth gets kidnapped
Gently then rehearsed, where the shadows talk back and the terror throw shade
And the guests on the panel look fresh from a side quest raid
We got chaos in the challenge, wisdom in the dark, a trope reward on the door
They still get in, but not far
If you're looking for a meaning, baby, you're right on track
Just don't ask Google, ask the voices whispering back
So loose in your halo, tight in your-
We're the only cove where the snacks are good
Welcome to the cold old psyche
Slightly
But like we're also not not we got candles lower and a membership spa
We got cosmic punch lines Astrology
T and the algorithm chained in the back making coffee your higher self
Please log in your lower cells here to try to sneak some sins the middle self
Oh, we just showed up for fun. None of us are whole babe. That's why we're one
Welcome to the Code of Psyche
Where the wild feels warm and biting
Where the truth comes out fighting biting
But damn, the lighting is exciting
Yeah, this is the Code of Psyche
Where the loss feels strangely mighty
You belong here, come nightly
Where the shadows glow
And the strange fits tightly
like the Empress for you, for the answers to your question, what does it tell me?
He should be nurturing you, he should be, he should be, and to like look at your also, you
know, make sure you're recognizing yourself, your own self-worth and everything. I just
Yeah, I mean it's like and also also watch out for pregnancy because that is like emperors is like kind of like
a lot of times an indicator of
pregnancy or fertility
Okay, so just keep an eye on that too. Okay
Oh, gosh. Oh, thank you, LaToya. Yeah, that's one of my songs. I do a lot of music. You can see my music
Guys, if you like whatever if you do like my music and a lot of people do like I do have like a lot of videos up
I do premiere a lot of it in my on the channel
Sometimes I see people come in like I do a lot of different stuff, you know, too, and I test a lot of stuff and so
but
Um, yeah, I'd love to see you at a premiere and stuff.
I may probably try to do new videos every day.
Not together.
So you just want to say that.
You're not together.
Well, he doesn't know what he's missing out on, right?
Well, oh shit, this is still the holidays.
Another video. Thank you. I'm glad you came like um
I do have a holiday video at Alexander McQueen's and oh, yeah, I'm in McDonald's
Yeah, this is like the old-fashioned kind of Christmas song, but it's not now. It's almost New Year's, but
Hey, might as well get a little bit more used out of it before I
Can't play it for no for another year
Let's see
desktop
Okay
Hmm
Sleigh bells ring the vibes feel cursed thing thought is his cranky
Thing that is as cranky like a cat in a wreath Side-eye so sharp it's cutting through my
piece King Carl is demanding more sparkle, more flair Like bro, I'm one person, I have
only two hands and a prayer God, it takes credit for everything we do
I invent it, holiday sir, you invent it being you Alexander got me McDonald's saving my soul
Jamie is mad at Mason, it's a season of beef
We're passin' around receipts like ornaments on a tree
Still no beta, what is this suffering?
We've been manifesting since Thanksgiving
Ghost is crashing out, the group chat's screaming
Come back, Alexandra we need you beaming
Fa la la la, please return ASAP
The cold is festive, but it's down bad
Ghost is crashing out like I'm done. I'm free then post a vague story. That's clearly about me
King Carl bangs the table. Where's the beta supply?
God is like I made beta. He's lying supplies
Thing that is his cranky won't bless the cocoa says this peppermint triggers my inner snow. No
Jamie won't talk to Mason unless there's mediation. So we schedule a healing circle holiday edition
Alexander's fries are cold, but the love is warm We're caroling in chaos, this is our norm
Still no beta, what is this suffering?
We've been manifesting since Thanksgiving
Ghost is crashing out, the group chat's screaming
Come back, Alexandra, we need you beaming
Fa la la la, please return ASAP
The cult is festive, but it's down bad
Okay, everybody breathe
One hand on heart, one hand on the McDonald's bag.
Repeat after me, I release the need to control.
I release the need for credit.
I release seasonal grudges. I invite people into this timeline.
And lastly, Alexandra, come back.
We are simply not stable without...
Still no beta, this is a tragedy
Someone call the North Pole's HR department please
Ghost is crashing out, Carl is demanding
Got himself awarding, Jamie's reprimanding
Fa la la la
Bring beta, too
Come back Alexandra, we miss you
Think that this is cranky, Carl once more
Gotti says, I did it, we can't take it anymore.
What a beautiful song.
Absolutely gorgeous song.
You like that?
Oh, the fries still are warm.
I love that.
A couple of those, like this, oh that's sweet and sour.
Sweet and sour. Kind of like Alexander.
Sweet and sour. Latoya. Yeah, it's just like somebody's on guard, like it could be you on guard.
No, but somebody's like...
I'm defensive like I don't know like looking like deciding whether to answer the phone or not sometimes
Or maybe like because you've been hurt so many times you expect maybe that he's doing something but
I think it's like maybe you're defensive that was Alexander thank you very much Alexander McQueen
for sponsoring my dinner tonight and thank you and that was awesome I really appreciate it I hadn't
Thank you Alexander
Welcome to the show
New subscribers and hopefully they didn't just see me like some embarrassing
Do you want some fry?
Do you want a fry?
Cat's eat fries?
Oh, Lola likes it.
There, have a fry.
Lola likes it.
Look.
She's eating the fry, but he's not here.
Yeah, try it.
It's good.
Good, yeah.
Kind of crazy show.
Your butt away from my frappuccino, please.
Oh, there you go.
I'll do a collective breed too after I finish eating.
Yeah, where's Lola Lola? She's down here eating it.
Are you eating the French fry down there?
See, it's not that terribly messy.
Yeah, there's the French fry down there.
Like, she like will eat lasagna.
I'm not sure if the card means yes or no.
Yeah, it's kind of like beyond guard too for yourself.
But it's like, cause it's like kind of like a weird question
with like how the cards are like, yeah,
they have like a lot of interpretations.
I just see just the image of the seven of wands
is like somebody on defense with like,
and they don't have a bandage on their head.
That's the nine of wands, but they have a,
but they still are just like still.
Locking their door or like squeaking their calls or something. I see like a lot of that. Oh, there's yeah
Tricks
She likes them
We really want them yeah, my friend the nor
Give us cat actors with our unit, you know who
Tartar sauces. There's so many named Tarver's tartar sauce
Tartar sauce is actually
Grumpy cat
Who else is their famous cat actor there's Sabrina the sale you know the Salem from Sabrina see you at teenage
Which that wasn't a really been real cat most of the time. It was an animatronic. Can you believe that? I?
Was it's devastating it was like worse of fighting out. There's no Santa. Well, there is a Santa and there's a Salem too
But he's in the kind of prop department
backstage at Sabrina the Teenage Witch show
Dress room
Yes
You know what I saw train cats?
It's like these Russian ladies had a circus.
And it was cats and the cats would just go across
like a little tightrope.
They'd kind of like just put like a little mouse
at the end of it and they kind of just run across it.
But basically it was like not that spectacular.
The cats would just like to get a cat to do anything.
It's like, you know, I don't need to see them
jump through a hoop, but they might have like,
you know, walked down like down the stage or something.
You know, it's like, hey, Summer, how are you?
Oh yeah, Summer is, I'll be my gym.
So I'm sorry.
to fix that. But I have modded everybody, but here you go.
Let's see. How are we doing, guys? Okay, here's my thing.
Because you're not even coming up on the
Let's see where it says, Add as much as we can over here.
Oh, here it is.
Here we go. Oh, that's so good. Oh, that was such a good McDonald's.
Did I finish it? Oh, I don't know. There's more. Oh my god.
Chicken nuggets. Oh, I got a lot of chicken nuggets.
Okay. Hey, Trix, you want a chicken nugget? I bet I like chicken nugget here.
you want some chicken nugget? share with me
oh you like that? oh you like that chicken nugget home
okay i got you home let me just get the chicken nugget oh there he is there he is oh there for
I'm just trying to break this deck in it's like so the cards are like very very very stiff
It's so sick. They're
Little bit
Truffle intensive
Hey black RG, how are you?
Gonna see everybody
Yeah
I'm still considering like, you know, cutting back my, my lives, you know, I took a day off
yesterday, I take a day off once in a while, um, which is like last year, I hardly took,
or this year, I hardly took any days off. And so just like a few, you know,
but it's good to do that because then you don't, you gotta get a chance to not burn out on it so
But it's everyone's been really cool today and it's like I
Have fun and thank you to everybody that
Summer let's see what we got here for you
Okay
People out these cards. Okay
Tennis stores, but it's like so really felt stabbed in the back about something
Okay
It's something to do with the communication and it seems like there's just like a lot of people involved too and it's like and then they're kind of like
Some opposite sides, right
But it's like they're not yeah, they're not seeing each other. Okay. Oh
We get this ace of wands, which is the ace of poles in this deck. Ace of wands is like this is like you got this kind of power
I'll tell you from the book ace of poles says the ace of poles
symbolizes fresh poaching to creative energy
you're full of visionary ideas, use the newly found inspiration to motivate you
and you'll be catapulted to an exciting adventure or exciting adventures, okay?
Seems like after like, you know, maybe you felt like stabbed in the back about something
There's like some kind of new thing offering or some kind of like something something came out of it
That is actually like and now it made you inspired to continue to do something. Let's see what else
It's in here. Okay, and then we got this 10 of cups. Okay, so this is like a long-term hap. Oh, where's the camera? Oh
One yeah, I'm on the wrong camera
Okay, this is the 10 of cups, right?
Which is like a long-term happiness. Okay, so it's like I think this is like whatever this is is gonna lead you to something
That will like basically make everyone very happy and like there's like a lot of sharing involved and like, you know
This I also see like, you know feet like feeding, you know feeding people like I like a lot like a lot of
because these are kind of like all these stoves and stuff with like the
Like food on the stove or something like that. Okay. I don't know if that's relevant for you, but
Oh, and then you got a seven, okay.
So also, but there's gonna be a lot of like opportunities.
And so you have to like choose like the right one
and stuff like that.
Cause some might not be as good as others,
but there's a lot of things like right now you're looking
at and maybe confused cause there's so many things, right?
Because, you know, there's like a lot of options
that can be overwhelming.
We have to just go for one at a time.
Maybe go for the biggest one first.
And then, you know, then the ones that you want after that,
but it's like, yeah, there's something to do
with emotions in this too.
Like you've got that fire,
but you've also got some emotions about going on too.
Okay, let me have the emperor.
So the emperor as a final card in your spread is very about being the boss.
I think, you know, whether it's you or your husband, I think you might share that responsibility
of both being the emperor, but I think that, you know, you definitely are the emperor in your life.
I'll tell you from the book what they say about this emperor because it's always interesting
to hear from the book about from the lab or the movie, right? So the emperor in the book,
It says, in traditional tarot, the Empress, the maternal figure is a counterpart of the
emperor, the paternal figure of the deck.
And such, Sarah's father is a natural fit to represent the author to.
um credit um tarot card yeah but her father was kind of a dick in that movie but it says but he
here he is like you can see he's there with fake the bottle and like the and so maybe it's about
also switching gender roles to or being able to be fluid in gender roles and that's like the real
being the real like you know emperor it's his comp it practical and level headed it kind of reminds
me of your husband then right the emperor is an expert leader who provides and up lifts upholds
get organized and practice self-discipline.
Okay, let me pull up one more card for you.
I just like give it a round out for the deck, okay?
I'm seeing that cups again.
I'm seeing like a lot of cups.
Yeah, I'm seeing like a lot of cups,
but I want to get a court card for you, okay?
The dancers, oh, this is a good one.
This is kind of like the lovers,
but this is the dancers.
It's like two people from the masquerade party,
you know, the dancers.
Also like maybe being able to play a role like being able to there's nothing with drama there
I think but it is a lover's card traditionally
Like all the dancers there, okay
It says
You're in total harmony with someone important in your life. This could refer to a romantic partner or a close friend or a
treasured family member. The tarot card also suggests you may soon find yourself at a crossroads.
Will you be dancing to dreamlike bliss forever or
is there more adventure out there waiting for you? Only you can decide. Trust your intuition.
We like that summer.
Summer's in a great song, by the way, called Summers the Getaway Driver.
There's a couple versions of it, I think I'll have to play that one.
Mr. B
one more door
They talk like profits, but trip on the map
Dropped all the mysteries right under the cat
But it's probably a song
Christine lost the plot of men to brought the wrong one
Summer missed the freeway, but she hit the gas anyway
Best worst crew ever doin' crime, adjacent cabaret
except to think of a Katrina song.
I think you might be in it.
With the petals we remember
I caught my shadow drinking moonlight from a broken chalice
He said, you're not who they name, you're who the storms remember
Lightning by the panda bird and the old gods whispered your forbidden title
I walked through the rows of forgotten saints
Their halos rusted, their prayers unmade
And each one rose as I passed